http://subscene.com/u/659433
Improved by: @Ivandrofly
(THEME MUSIC PLAYING)
Sync & corrections by
honeybunny www.addic7ed.com
(LATCH CLANKS)
What are they doing
with the bodies?
Get back to work.
No. I've been
here for weeks.
I'm not scrubbing
one more corpse
until you tell me
why I'm doing it.
You will know why.
- When?
- When it's time, not before.
Get back to work.
When do I get to play the game?
Game?
The game. The
Game of Faces.
You tried already.
You failed.
I didn't even know
I was playing.
Who are you?
No one.
Get back to work.
Who are you?
What are you doing here?
How did you get here?
I'm from Westeros just like you.
Daughter of a
lord just like you.
Except I was an only child.
Heir to his fortune.
My mother died.
My father remarried
and his new wife
gave birth to a girl.
My stepmother didn't want any
rivals for her precious daughter,
so she tried to kill
me with poison.
I found out.
Sought help from
the Faceless Men.
And my father was widowed again.
I've been serving
them ever since.
Was that true or a lie?
What?
Did you believe
every word I said?
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
Get back to work.
JAQEN: Who are you?
Who are you?
Arya.
And where did you come from?
Westeros.
My family home is Winterfell.
I'm the youngest
daughter of a great lord,
Eddard Stark.
He died in battle.
A lie.
After he was executed,
I fled the capital.
Had to kill a stable boy.
Drove my sword through his back.
(GASPS)
A lie.
I stabbed him in the gut.
I tried to find
my mother and brother,
but I never did.
They were murdered
by Walder Frey.
An outlaw kidnapped me,
a man called Polliver.
(WINCES)
A man called the
Hound. Sandor Clegane.
He tried to sell me, but
was wounded in a fight.
He begged me to kill
him, but I wouldn't.
I left him in the
mountains to die.
I wanted him to
suffer. I hated him.
I hated him.
That's not a lie!
A girl lies to me,
to the Many-Faced
God, to herself.
Does she truly
want to be no one?
Yes.
(WHIMPERS)
I'm not playing this
stupid game anymore!
We never stop playing.
So, those villages we
were supposed to find?
We can't live on
berries and roots.
I can.
You're not hungry?
Of course I'm hungry.
You're an awful travelling
companion, do you know that?
Possibly the least charming
man I've ever met.
I'm not your
travelling companion.
We are travelling together in each
other's company, therefore--
Do you ever shut up?
I sailed from King's Landing
to Pentos in a crate
without ever saying a word.
Why?
It never occurred to you
to ask why until now?
You never wondered
why Tyrion Lannister
decided to visit a
brothel in Volantis?
I'm sure you visited many
brothels in many cities.
I killed my father.
He wanted to execute me
for a crime I didn't commit.
And he was fucking
the woman I loved.
As miserable as
you are, Mormont,
at least your father
was a good man.
What do you know
about my father?
I met him. I
visited the Wall.
When I asked him about his men,
he knew all their stories,
every one of them.
He actually cared about the
people under his command.
How do they put it in the Watch?
"We shall never
see his like again."
Oh, you didn't know.
I'm sorry.
I am.
How?
I only know what I heard.
He was leading an
expedition beyond the Wall.
There was a mutiny.
He was murdered by his own men.
We better keep moving.
Valar morghulis.
Valar dohaeris.
I have nowhere else to go.
I've taken her to every
healer in Braavos.
I've spent every penny I had.
(LABORED BREATHING)
She suffers every
day of her life.
I just want it to end.
It hurts.
I know.
Don't be afraid.
I used to be like you.
I was sick.
I was dying.
But my father never
gave up on me.
He loved me
more than anything in the world,
just like your father loves you.
So he brought me here.
My father prayed to
the Many-Faced God.
And I drank the water
from his fountain.
It healed me.
(BOWL SCRAPES)
I've devoted my life to him now.
You don't want to hurt anymore?
Drink.
JAQEN: Is a girl ready?
To give up her ears,
her nose, her tongue?
Her hopes and dreams,
her loves and hates?
All that makes a
girl who she is?
Forever?
No.
A girl is not ready
to become no one.
But she is ready to
become someone else.
Why Daenerys? Why
is she worth all this?
As I recall, the Mormonts
fought against the Targaryens
during Robert's Rebellion.
Do you believe in anything?
I believe in lots of things.
In something greater
than ourselves, I mean.
The gods, destiny.
Do you believe there's
a plan for this world?
No.
Neither did I.
I was a cynic just like you.
Then I saw a girl
step into a great fire
with three stone eggs.
When the fire burned out, I thought
I'd find her blackened bones.
Instead, I saw her, Daenerys,
alive and unhurt, holding
her baby dragons.
Have you ever heard
baby dragons singing?
No.
It's hard to be a
cynic after that.
Doesn't mean she's going
to be a great queen.
No, it doesn't.
The Targaryens are
famously insane.
What if she conquers
the world? Then what?
1,000 years of peace
and prosperity?
First we have to
conquer the world.
We?
All right, let's assume
your dreams come true.
She's ecstatic when you
bring her this enemy dwarf.
She hacks off my head
and restores your position.
You command her
army, sail to Westeros,
defeat all your enemies and
watch her climb those steps
and sit on the Iron Throne.
Hurrah. Long live the
queen. Then what?
Then she rules.
So a woman who has not spent
a single day of her adult life
in Westeros becomes the ruler
of Westeros? That's justice?
- She's the rightful heir.
- Why?
Because her father, who burned living
men for amusement, was the king?
- That's a slave ship.
- Why are they anchored?
They probably
came ashore for--
-  (SWORDS SCRAPING)
- MAN: Water.
- (GRUNTS)
- (MAN LAUGHS)
Got a lot of fight in you, huh?
(GRUNTS)
(CHUCKLES)
Salt mines?
Yeah, that or a galley slave.
He looks strong enough.
What about the dwarf?
Worthless.
Cut his throat.
Wait. Wait. Wait, wait,
wait! Let's discuss this.
And then chop off his cock.
We'll sell it for a fortune.
A dwarf's cock has magic powers.
Wait! Wait!
Wait, wait, wait!
You can't just hand a
dry cock to a merchant
and expect him to pay for it.
He has to know it
came from a dwarf.
And how could he know
unless he sees the dwarf?
It will be a
dwarf-sized cock.
Guess again.
The dwarf lives until we
find a cock merchant.
(EXHALES)
Queen Daenerys has
outlawed slavery.
We're bound for Volantis,
not Slaver's Bay.
Besides, she reopened
the fighting pits.
I've never heard of free
men fighting in the pits.
TYRION: The fighting
pits in Meereen?
You're in luck, then.
You're about to be rich.
You are looking at one of the great
warriors in the Seven Kingdoms.
(LAUGHS)
Him.
Him? He's got to
be 60 years old.
Sure, he's a bit
long in the tooth,
a bit withered, been
in the sun too long.
We can all see that. But he
is a veteran of 100 battles.
They wrote songs about him.
That true?
He won the tournament
at Lannisport.
Unseating Ser Jaime
Lannister himself.
- (LAUGHS)
- The Kingslayer.
Jousting. You're
talking about jousting.
A fancy game for fancy lads.
The men who fight in the pits of
Meereen will swallow him whole.
I killed a Dothraki
bloodrider in single combat.
Liar.
It's no lie. His
name was Qotho.
He was bloodrider to Khal Drogo.
Take me to Slaver's Bay,
put a sword in my hand,
I'll prove my worth.
(LAUGHING)
-  (SEAGULLS SCREECHING)
- (BELL RINGING)
For my children.
Money.
Lord Baelish.
Yes?
Lancel Lannister.
Brother Lancel.
We abandon our family names.
Quite a family to abandon.
The city has changed
since you were here last.
We flooded the
gutters with wine,
smashed the false idols,
and set the godless on the run.
Well done.
I'm here on urgent business
for the Queen Mother.
Should I send word
that I'll be delayed?
Step carefully, Lord Baelish.
You'll find there's little
tolerance for flesh peddlers
in the new King's Landing.
We both peddle
fantasies, Brother Lancel.
Mine just happen
to be entertaining.
Do you think it's
wise, Your Grace,
arresting the heir
to Highgarden?
The Faith arrested the
heir to Highgarden.
Of course, and the Faith
were armed on your orders.
The king's orders.
Is the king to blame for
Ser Loras's perversion?
House Tyrell won't
tolerate this insult.
House Tyrell won't tolerate it?
I'm the insulted
party, Lord Baelish.
Ser Loras was promised to me.
Instead he chose the
company of boys.
One's choice of companion
is a curious thing.
Most curious.
Lysa Arryn, for instance.
Thoroughly repellant woman.
Forgive me.
I know you're still in mourning.
Lysa was a good woman.
A kind woman.
She was neither of those things.
We both know it.
Still, I pity her son.
How fortunate the
young Lord of the Vale
has a new father to counsel him.
I know how hard it can be
to lose both your parents
at such a young age.
If war comes to Westeros, will the
Knights of the Vale fight for their king?
Young Lord Robin
heeds my advice.
And I have always counseled
loyalty to the throne.
Good.
If there's nothing else.
There is another
matter, Your Grace.
Something so urgent I couldn't
trust the words to a raven.
You once charged me
with finding Arya Stark.
To my shame, I failed you.
But I have found Sansa Stark.
Alive and well and home again
living at Winterfell.
That's not possible.
My sources are well placed.
They tell me Roose Bolton
plans to marry her
to his son Ramsay,
a bastard recently
legitimized by King Tommen.
Roose Bolton is Warden of the
North by the grace of my father.
Indeed, his reward for stabbing
his own king in the heart.
We were fools to
trust a turncloak.
Marrying his son to
the last of the Starks
gives him more
legitimacy in the North
than an alliance with a
hated southern house.
I will skin him and his bastard
like that wretch on
their bloody sigil.
I would counsel
patience, Your Grace.
Patience?
Sansa helped murder my son.
Roose Bolton is a traitor.
Stannis Baratheon
is also a traitor,
marching with his
army on Winterfell.
Let Stannis and Roose battle.
Let the enemies of the
throne slaughter each other.
And when they're done, seize Winterfell
from whichever thief survives.
Winterfell is 1,000
miles away from here.
The weather has
already begun to turn.
That is why it is
critical to strike soon
while the victor still
licks his wounds.
Surely your Uncle Kevan
could muster a force.
My Uncle Kevan has all the
courage of a kitchen mouse.
Ser Jaime, then.
Jaime's away on a sensitive
diplomatic mission.
I have no idea
when he'll be back.
Perhaps I can help.
The Knights of the Vale are some
of the best fighters in Westeros,
trained to battle in
the ice and the snow.
Forgive me, Lord Baelish,
you have a reputation
as a moneylender
and a brothel keeper,
not a military man.
You wouldn't risk a
single Lannister soldier
or a single coin from
the royal treasury.
What do you have to lose?
A brothel keeper?
And if you succeed?
Name me Warden of the North.
I'll speak to the
king this evening,
have him issue a royal decree.
I'll not rest until the lion
flies over Winterfell.
And I'll know you're
a man of your word
when I see Sansa
Stark's head on a spike.
As I said...
I live to serve.
I'm going to ask him tomorrow.
- What if he says no?
- He won't.
We've waited long enough.
I want you to be my wife.
Now.
What is it?
Do you want to marry me
because our families arranged it?
Or do you--
We can't.
Not yet.
Why not?
You know why not.
Someone will see.
You are going to be my wife.
I am going to be your husband.
We're allowed to walk
through the gardens together.
How many other girls have you
walked through these gardens?
I like the way your eyes go
squinty when you're jealous.
They do not go squinty and
you didn't answer the question.
DORAN: They make
a lovely couple.
A Lannister and a Martell.
They have no idea
how dangerous that is.
We must protect them.
Yes, my prince.
You haven't had to use that
axe of yours in a long time.
I hope you remember how.
I remember how.
♪ BRONN: The Dornishman's ♪
♪ wife was as fair as the sun  ♪
♪ And her kisses were ♪
♪ warmer than spring ♪
♪ The Dornishman's blade ♪
♪ It was made of black steel ♪
♪ And its kiss was ♪
♪ a terrible thing ♪
♪ The Dornishman's wife ♪
♪ would sing as she bathed ♪
- ♪ In a voice that was sweet as a ♪
♪ peach-- - All right, that's enough. ♪
I'm coming to the best part.
We're trying to blend in.
Don't want everyone in
Dorne to hear your accent.
This song really is
all about the ending.
It can wait.
There.
That's the Water Gardens.
BRONN: And once we've got
the princess, then what?
(SIGHS)
I like to improvise.
That explains the golden hand.
ELLARIA: Unbowed.
Unbent. Unbroken.
For Oberyn.
ALL: For
Oberyn.
Well, she's made
herself at home.
Myrcella.
Uncle Jaime?
I--
I don't understand. What
are you doing here?
Let's speak in private.
- I am Trystane Martell.
- Trystane is my intended.
Excellent. Good
to meet you.
We weren't expecting
you, Lord Jaime.
Why don't you let them
have some time alone, son?
Let's not do something stupid.
(GRUNTS)
- (SHRIEKS)
- That was something stupid.
We have to go, Myrcella, now.
- You hurt him!
- He'll be fine, I promise.
But we have to--
(GRUNTS)
Oh, for fuck's sake.
(SHOUTING)
(WHIP CRACKS)
Take her!
- You're coming with me.
- I don't want to.
I wasn't asking, princess.
(SCREAMS)
- Ah!
- Drop your weapons!
OBARA: I am Obara Sand.
Daughter of Oberyn Martell.
I fight for Dorne.
Who do you fight for?
Drop your weapons.
When you were whole, it
would have been a good fight.
(SWORD CLATTERS)
You fight pretty
good for a little girl.
(SHOUTING)
- (HORSES NEIGHING)
-  (SEAGULLS SCREECHING)
Halt!
Oh, you can smell the
shit from five miles away.
Well, why have we
stopped? Go on.
(HORSES NEIGHING)
Rumors and gossip,
that's all they've got.
It's theater, nothing more.
If they arrested all the pillow
biters in King's Landing,
there'd be no room left in the
dungeons for anyone else.
Everyone knew
about him and Renly.
Renly Baratheon shagged half the
stable boys in the Seven Kingdoms.
Everyone knew, no one cared.
But he was the king's brother.
And Loras is the
queen's brother.
No, no, no, no. This
is unacceptable.
- Cersei's behind it.
- Yeah, of course she is.
She wants to drag our
name through the dirt,
put us in our place.
Get some rest, dear.
You look appalling.
Let me deal with
Cersei Lannister.
(TAPPING)
Your Grace, I have
travelled a long way.
You must be exhausted.
Put the pen down, dear. We both
know you're not writing anything.
Ah, yes. The famously
tart-tongued Queen of Thorns.
And the famous
tart Queen Cersei.
I beg your pardon?
I know you're behind this absurd
incarceration of my grandson.
If you apologize for that
comment, perhaps I'll--
You'll get your apology
when I get Loras.
I was as shocked as anyone
when the Faith
arrested Ser Loras.
I have no love for
these fanatics,
but what can a Queen Mother do?
Has the crown suddenly
stopped needing
the troops, gold, and
wheat my house supplies?
I can assure you,
our alliance with
House Tyrell remains--
Do you expect the
alliance to continue
after you've thrown
our future into prison?
As I said,
I didn't imprison anyone.
As for your
veiled threats--
What veil?
(SIGHS)
The Lannister-Tyrell alliance brought
peace to a war-torn country.
Do you really want to see the Seven
Kingdoms slide back into warfare?
I didn't trust your father.
I didn't particularly like him.
But I respected him.
He was no fool.
He understood that sometimes
we must work with our rivals
rather than destroy them.
House Lannister has no rival.
The High Septon has called
for an inquest, not a trial.
Just a small hearing
to determine
whether the charges
against Loras have merit,
which I'm sure they don't.
Loras will be freed, our
happy alliance will continue...
and we'll forget this unfortunate
conversation ever happened.
Good day, Lady Olenna.
(DOOR OPENS, CLOSES)
You are aware of the rumors
concerning you and Renly?
I don't pay attention to rumors.
You were said to be
despondent when he died.
Witnesses state that you
refused to leave his bedside
even as Stannis's
army closed in.
He was my friend.
He was my king.
Wasn't Joffrey your king?
He was anointed
by the Seven, not Renly.
I was wrong to support
Renly's claim, I know that.
But I was forgiven by Joffrey.
I fought for him at the
Battle of Blackwater.
Yes, wearing Renly's armor.
Why does it matter what I wore?
Do you deny all the
charges against you?
Fornication.
Buggery.
Blasphemy.
Of course I deny them.
You never lay with
Renly Baratheon?
Never.
Nor any other man?
That will be all, Ser Loras.
Well, I think that's
quite enough of that.
The Faith calls Queen
Margaery forward.
You call me forward?
Yes, we have some
questions for you.
- I am the queen.
- You are.
And according to the
law of the Seven,
neither kings nor
queens are exempt
from testimony
at a holy inquest.
How do you respond to these
charges against your brother?
They are lies.
- All of them?
- All of them.
HIGH SPARROW: Queen Margaery,
in the presence of the gods,
do you swear that your
brother is innocent
of these charges against him
to the best of your knowledge?
Yes, I swear it.
Thank you, Your Grace.
Do you know this man?
Yes, very well.
He is Ser Loras Tyrell,
heir to Highgarden.
How did you come to meet?
OLYVAR: I squired for him.
He took a liking to me.
He summoned me to his
chamber the first day we met.
And what occurred
in his chamber?
We engaged in
intimate relations.
You lay with him?
That night and many others.
Liar. He's
a liar.
Is there anyone else who
can support your claim?
Yes.
Yes, Queen Margaery.
She walked in on us once
not long ago.
She didn't seem surprised.
This testimony is an
insult to a great house.
Why should the Faith or anyone
else take the word of a squire
over the heir to Highgarden?
OLYVAR: He has a
birthmark, Your Grace.
Quite high on his thigh.
Wine-colored and roughly
the shape of Dorne.
No! Liar!
(GRUNTING)
What are you
doing? Let us pass.
The Faith is satisfied
there is enough evidence
to bring a formal trial
for Ser Loras
and Queen Margaery.
What?
Bearing false witness
before the gods
is as grave a sin
as any, my lady.
Take her.
MARGAERY: No. Tommen.
Tommen!
You can't do this.
I am the queen.
Tommen!
I am your queen.
How dare you?
Take your hands off me!
(SHOUTING)
Tommen!
(KNOCKS ON DOOR)
(WIND WHISTLING)
What do you want?
Lord Ramsay sent me to
draw you a bath, my lady.
You want to be clean and fresh
for your new husband, don't you?
You're so beautiful,
but you need to keep him happy.
Ramsay gets bored easily.
You don't want
to end up like--
well, like the others.
What others?
MYRANDA: I
shouldn't gossip.
Oh, it's good to
see the red again.
No point hiding anymore.
What others?
Let's see, there was Kyra
the blacksmith's daughter.
She was tall like
you, lovely figure.
But she talked and
talked and talked
and Ramsay grew tired of that.
Then there was Violet.
She had gorgeous blonde hair.
But she got pregnant.
And, well, that was boring.
Then Tansy.
Such a sweet girl.
Of course, sweet
girls get a bit dull
after a while, don't they?
Ramsay let me come
with him on that hunt.
Hunt?
Mmm.
Have you ever seen a body
after the dogs have been at it?
Not so pretty.
But, well, it's your
wedding day.
Why am I talking
about such things?
What was your name again?
Myranda.
And how long have yo
loved him, Myranda?
Did you imagine that he would
be with you forever, is that it?
And I came along and ruined it.
I'm Sansa Stark of Winterfell.
This is my home and
you can't frighten me.
Are you done with
your bath, my lady?
Go. I can finish
on my own.
-  (KNOCKS ON DOOR)
- Yes?
I've come to escort you to
the godswood, my lady.
If you please, my lady,
will you take my arm?
No.
Lord Ramsay, he said
I'm to take your arm.
I'm not touching you.
Please.
He'll punish me.
You think I care
what he does to you?
Who comes before the
old gods this night?
THEON: Sansa of
the House Stark
comes here to be wed.
A woman grown,
trueborn and noble.
She comes to beg the
blessings of the gods.
Who comes to claim her?
Ramsay of House Bolton.
Heir to the Dreadfort
and Winterfell.
Who gives her?
Theon of House
Greyjoy, who was--
who was her father's ward.
Lady Sansa, will
you take this man?
I take this man.
Are you pleased, my lady?
Good. I want
you to be happy.
(SIGHS)
My father said
you're still a virgin.
- Uh, yes.
- Why?
Why are you still a virgin?
Afraid of dwarves?
Lord-- Lord Tyrion was kind.
He was gentle. He
never touched me.
You're not lying to me?
No, my lord.
Lying to your husband
on his wedding night,
that would be a bad
way to start a marriage.
We're man and wife now.
We should be honest
with each other.
Don't you think?
Yes.
Good.
Take off your clothes.
Oh, no, no, no.
You stay here, Reek.
You watch.
Do I need to ask a second time?
I hate asking a second time.
Reek...
I told you to watch.
You've known Sansa
since she was a girl.
Now watch her become a woman.
(GASPS)
(CLOTHES RIPPING)
(WHIMPERING)
- (BREATHING QUICKLY)
-  (BELT BUCKLE CLINKING)
-  (RAMSAY GRUNTING)
- (SANSA GROANING)
(SANSA CRYING)
Sync & corrections by
honeybunny www.addic7ed.com
http://subscene.com/u/659433
Improved by: @Ivandrofly