♪ Theme music playing  ♪
♪ Game of Thrones 4x10 ♪
The Children
Original Air Date on June 15, 2014
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ Theme music ends  ♪
( cawing )
( dog barking )
You're wearing
a black cloak again.
I've been sent
to negotiate with you.
It appears my trusting
nature got the better of me.
It's happened before.
I was hoping your loyalty
was real
when you pledged
yourself to us, Jon Snow.
Truly I was.
The Halfhand ordered me
to join your army
and bring back whatever
information I could to Castle Black.
He made me kill him
so you'd trust me.
I was loyal...
to him and to my
Night's Watch vows.
All your vows?
She wasn't enough
to turn you, eh?
Were you enough
to turn her?
She put three
arrows in me
when I escaped.
Did you see her
again at Castle Black?
- Yes.
- And?
She's dead.
- Your doing?
- No.
We'll drink to her.
Of all the ways
I'd kill you,
poison would be
the last.
- Ygritte.
( coughs )
That's not wine.
No, it's a proper
northern drink, Jon Snow.
You did well.
Fought hard.
Killed some of
our strongest men.
One of our giants
went into your tunnel
and never
came out again.
Mag the Mighty.
He's dead.
He killed
my friend Grenn.
He was their king.
The last of a bloodline
that stretches back
before the First Men.
Grenn came from a farm.
- Mag and Grenn.
- Grenn and Mag.
Kullback, could I trouble
you for something to eat?
I don't imagine our guest
has eaten anything
for quite some time.
So, you're here
to strike a bargain?
Turn your army around
and go home.
You know I know
you're low on arrows,
you're low on oil,
you're low on men.
How many are left, 50?
I told Tormund and Orell.
We have more
than 1,000 men.
I showed you
everything I had.
The whole army,
100,000 strong.
And what did you do?
You fired on us with
everything you had.
It wasn't much.
As soon as I saw that,
I sent 400 men
to climb the Wall,
an unmanned stretch
five miles west of here.
A lot of them
will die climbing,
but most of them will be
over by the end of the day.
It's me being honest
with you, Jon Snow,
which is more than
you've ever done for me.
My people
have bled enough.
We're not here
to conquer.
We're here to hide
behind your Wall.
Just like you.
We need your tunnel.
Now we both know
that winter is coming.
And if my people aren't south
of the Wall when it comes in earnest,
we'll all end up
worse than dead.
You want to strike
a bargain with me?
Here's the bargain.
You go back,
you open the gates to us,
and I swear to you
that no one else will die.
Refuse,
and we'll kill every
last man at Castle Black.
Ah!
Oh, that's why
you're here.
I reckon you could do it before
any of them could stop you.
They'd kill you,
of course.
They'd kill you slow.
But you knew that
when you came in here.
Are you capable
of that, Jon Snow?
Killing a man in his own tent
when he's just offered you peace?
Is that what
the Night's Watch is?
Is that what you are?
- ( horn blows )
- Man: Riders coming!
- Are you attacking us?
- No.
It's like you said,
we don't have the men.
- ( horn blowing )
- ( dogs barking )
( men shouting )
( horse whinnies )
Hold! To me!
To me!
( men shouting )
Stand down!
I said my people
have bled enough
and I meant it.
( shouting )
Man:
Round them up.
Stay with the horses.
You're the
King-beyond-the-Wall?
- Do you know who I am?
- Never had the pleasure.
This is Stannis Baratheon,
the one true king
of the Seven Kingdoms.
We're not in the Seven Kingdoms and
you're not dressed for this weather.
It is customary to kneel
when surrendering to a king.
We do not kneel.
I'll have thousands of your men
in chains by nightfall,
have nowhere to put them,
have nothing to feed them.
I'm not here
to slaughter beat dogs.
Their fate
depends on their king.
All the same,
we do not kneel.
Take these men away.
What's a man of the Night's Watch
doing in a wildling camp?
I was sent to discuss terms with the
King-beyond-the-Wall.
You're speaking
to the one true king, boy.
You will address him
as Your Grace.
I know he's the king.
My father died for him.
My name is Jon Snow,
Your Grace.
I'm Ned Stark's son.
Your father
was an honorable man.
He was, Your Grace.
What do you think
he'd have done with him?
I was this man's
prisoner once.
He could have tortured me.
He could have killed me.
But he spared my life.
I think my father would
have taken him prisoner,
listened to what
he had to say.
Very well, then.
Take him.
Your Grace.
If my father had seen
the things that I've seen,
he'd also tell you to burn the dead
before nightfall.
All of them.
( flies buzzing )
I would suggest
milk of the poppy
to ease his pain,
but he is completely insensate.
Bloody Martells.
The cause appears
to be manticore venom.
It is.
The Death's Head manticore.
Yes, I've read
a great deal about it.
It's a horrible poison.
Usually Mantari
in origin.
Oh! Yes, yes.
There's nothing
to be done.
Yes, there is.
May I ask what you
think you're doing?
Saving him.
Your Grace, I wish
it were otherwise,
but Ser Gregor
is beyond saving.
Well, well beyond.
This man is not
even a maester,
let alone Grand Maester.
That's for the best.
No maester knows
how to save him.
That is exactly
the sort of arrogance
that had him expelled from
the Citadel, Your Grace.
His curiosity was deemed
dangerous and unnatural.
Rightly so,
in my opinion.
You're dismissed,
Grand Maester.
But, Your Grace,
this is my laboratory.
- Not anymore.
- Pycelle: But I--
( scoffs )
( door opens )
- You can save him?
- Difficult to say, Your Grace.
But if my past work
is any guide...
( door slams )
...we stand a chance.
Do everything you can.
Come to me
for anything you need.
Thank you,
Your Grace.
You should know,
the process
may change him...
somewhat.
Will it weaken him?
Oh, no.
Very well, then.
Tywin:
Not another word.
We've been over this.
The matter's closed.
I'm opening it again.
You were betrothed
to Loras Tyrell.
You're still betrothed
And you will marry
Loras Tyrell
as soon as Tommen
marries Margaery.
I will not.
Jaime cannot marry
or inherit lands.
Tyrion's sentence
will be carried out tomorrow.
You have on several occasions
made great claims
about your commitment
to this family's future.
Your role in that future
is more vital now
than it ever was.
I don't care.
I will stay in King's Landing
where I belong with my son the king.
When you were nine years old,
I was called to the capital.
I decided to take your brother
with me and not you.
You insisted that you would not be
left at Casterly Rock
under any circumstances.
And if you recall--
I'm not interested in hearing
another one of your smug stories
about the time you won.
This isn't going to be
one of those times.
Do you think
you'll be the first person
dragged into a sept to be
married against her will?
When you marched into
the throne room to tell me
we'd won the Battle of Blackwater--
do you remember?
I was sitting on the Iron
Throne with Tommen.
I was about to give him
essence of nightshade.
That's how far I was willing to go
when I thought
someone awful had come
to take my son away.
Someone awful is coming
to take him away.
- No.
- Joffrey is dead.
Myrcella's been sold
like livestock.
And now you want to ship me off
to Highgarden and steal my boy.
My last boy.
Margaery will dig
her claws in,
you will dig your claws in
and you'll fight over him
like beasts
until you rip him apart.
I will burn our house to the ground
before I let that happen.
And how will you do that?
I'll tell
everyone the truth.
What truth
would that be?
You don't know, do you?
You never believed it.
How is that possible?
What am I saying?
Of course it's possible.
How can someone so consumed
by the idea of his family
have any conception
what his actual family was doing?
We were right there
in front of you and you didn't see us.
One look
in the past 20 years,
one real look at your own children
and you would have known.
Known what?
Everything they say
is true.
- About Jaime and me.
- No.
- Your legacy is a lie.
- No, no, no, no.
I don't believe you.
Yes, you do.
Jaime.
You won.
One fewer brother.
Must be proud of yourself.
There's really nothing
you wouldn't do, is there?
For my family,
no, nothing.
I would do things for my family you
couldn't imagine.
- Tyrion is your family.
- He's not.
- You don't get to choose.
- I do. So do you.
You can choose the creature that killed
our mother to come into this world--
Are you really mad enough
to blame him for that?
He didn't decide to kill her.
He was an infant.
A disease doesn't decide
to kill you.
All the same, you cut it out
before it does.
What do you decide?
What do you choose?
The things I did
to get back to you,
to endure all that,
only to find you--
I choose you.
- Those are words.
- Yes.
Like the ones
I just said to Father.
I told him.
Told him what?
I told him about us.
You told him?
I told him I won't
marry Loras Tyrell.
I told him I'm staying
right here with Tommen, with you.
You think he'll
just accept that?
Go and ask him.
What did you say?
I don't want to talk
about Tywin Lannister.
I don't choose
Tywin Lannister.
I don't love
I love my brother.
I love my lover.
People will whisper,
they'll make their jokes.
Let them.
They're all so small,
I can't even see them.
I only see what matters.
Someone will walk in.
I don't care.
( Missandei speaking
Valyrian )
( speaking Valyrian )
I can speak the common
tongue if you wish.
You speak it very well.
Before you freed me,
I belonged to Master Mighdal.
I was tutor
to his children.
I taught them languages
and history.
They know a great deal
about your family because of me.
Little Calla
is only seven,
but she admires you
very much.
I hope I can prove
worthy of her admiration.
What can I do for you?
When you took the city,
the children begged me
not to leave the house.
But Master Mighdal
and I agreed that I must.
So I lost my home.
Now I live on the streets.
I have outfitted mess halls
to feed all former slaves
and barracks to shelter them.
I do not mean
to offend, Your Grace.
I went to one
of these places.
The young prey on the old.
Take what they want
and beat us if we resist.
My Unsullied will make them
safe again in short order,
my friend,
this I promise you.
Even if they are safe,
who would I be there?
What purpose
would I serve?
With my master,
I was a teacher.
I had the respect
and love of his children.
What is it
that you want from me?
Your Grace, I ask you
to let me sell myself
back to Master Mighdal.
You want to return
to a man who owned you
like a goat
or a chair?
Please, Your Grace.
The young may rejoice in the
new world you have built for them,
but for those of us
too old to change,
there is only fear
and squalor.
I am not alone.
There are many outside waiting
to beg the same of you.
I did not take
this city to preside
over the injustice
I fought to destroy.
I took it to bring
people freedom.
But freedom means making
your own choices.
I will allow you to sign a contract
with your former master.
It may not cover a period
lasting longer than a year.
Thank you, Your Grace.
Thank you.
The masters will take advantage
of this situation.
The men serving them
will be slaves
in all but name.
Approach, my friend.
( speaking Low Valyrian )
( sobbing )
( speaking low Valyrian )
Missandei:
I have brought you--
He came from the sky.
The black one.
The winged shadow.
He came from
the sky and...
My girl.
My little girl.
( sobbing )
Daenerys:
What was her name?
Missandei:
Zala, Your Grace.
- How old was she?
- Three.
Three.
( speaking Valyrian )
( Grey Worm speaking
Valyrian )
( speaking Valyrian )
( screeching )
( roaring )
Aemon: They came to us from White
Harbor and Barrowton,
from Fairmarket
and King's Landing,
from north and south,
from east and west.
They died protecting
men, women, and children
who will never know
their names.
It is for us
to remember them.
Our brothers,
we shall never see
their like again.
All: And now their watch
is ended.
Aemon: And now their watch
Your old blind man
patched me up.
Why?
He's sworn to treat all
wounded men, friend or foe.
You want me alive
so you can torture me?
No one's gonna torture you.
So how do we die?
Hanging? Beheading?
Drop us from the top
of the Wall?
I don't know what happens
to the prisoners.
Who decides?
I suppose Stannis does.
He your king now?
I don't have a king.
You spent too much
time with us, Jon Snow.
You can never be
a kneeler again.
We're gonna burn
the bodies of your dead.
Do you want to say
any words over them?
Words?
What kind of words?
Funeral words. I don't know how
the free folk do it.
Do what?
Say farewell.
The dead can't
hear us, boy.
Snow.
Did you love her?
She loved you.
She told you?
No.
All she ever talked about
was killing you.
That's how I know.
She belongs
in the North.
The real North.
You understand me?
( wind howling )
( groaning )
We can stop.
We can rest.
We'll rest with
the three-eyed raven.
We're not
going to make it.
We're already here.
Bran:
Jojen.
Look, Jojen.
Look.
( groaning )
Jojen!
Come on!
Help them!
Now!
Meera:
Hold on to me!
Hang on!
- Hodor.
- Help them!
Hodor.
- ( growling )
- Hodor!
( screeching )
( grunts )
Hodor!
( growling )
Hodor.
( whimpering )
Hodor!
Jojen:
Bran!
Save yourself, now!
( grunting )
( shouts )
Girl: Come with me,
Brandon Stark.
( gasping )
He is lost.
Come with me
or die with him.
Go with them.
( ice bursting )
( slices )
( growling )
They cannot follow us.
The power that moves them
is powerless here.
Who are you?
The First Men
called us the children,
but we were born
long before them.
Come, he waits for you.
( crow caws )
( caws )
You're the three-eyed raven?
I've been many things.
Now I am what you see.
My brother, he led us to you
and now he--
He knew
what would happen.
From the moment
he left,
he knew
and he went anyway.
How do you know?
I've been watching you.
All of you.
All of your lives.
With 1,000 eyes
and one.
Now you've come
to me at last,
Brandon Stark.
Though the hour is late.
I didn't want
anyone to die for me.
He died so you could find
what you have lost.
You're going to help
me walk again?
You will never
walk again.
But you will fly.
( bird squawks )
Podrick.
Where are the horses?
I hobbled them
last night.
What sort of hobble?
A figure eight
like you taught me.
If you did it
like I taught you,
then the horses
would be here.
Thieves, maybe?
It's at least 30 miles
to the Eyrie from here.
You're carrying
the saddlebags.
( grunting )
People coming.
You can shit later.
There's people coming.
Morning.
I like your sword.
Are we getting close
to the Bloody Gate?
About 10 more miles.
Did you
hear that, Podrick?
Only 10 more miles
to the Bloody Gate.
Are you a knight?
No.
But you know how
to use that sword?
I do.
Does it have a name?
Oathkeeper.
Mine's Needle.
Good name.
Who taught you
how to fight?
My father.
Mine never wanted to.
Said fighting
was for boys.
Mine said the same.
But I kept fighting
the boys anyway.
Kept losing.
Finally my father said,
"If you're going to do it,
you might as well
do it right."
Seven blessings.
I'm Brienne of Tarth.
This is Podrick Payne.
You want something?
That's Sandor Clegane.
The Hound.
You're Arya Stark.
I asked if you
wanted something.
I swore to your mother
I would bring you home to her.
My mother's dead.
I know.
I wish I could have
been there to protect her.
You're not a northerner.
No, but I swore a sacred
vow to protect her.
Why didn't you?
She commanded me to bring
Jaime Lannister back to King's Landing.
You're paid
by the Lannisters.
You're here
for the bounty on me.
I'm not paid
by the Lannisters.
No?
Fancy sword
you've got there.
Where'd you get it?
I've been looking
at Lannister gold all my life.
Go on, Brienne
of fucking Tarth.
Tell me that's not
Lannister gold.
Jaime Lannister
gave me this sword.
The Bloody Gate
is 10 miles.
I swore to your mother
by the old gods--
I don't care
what you swore.
- Arya!
- Hound: You heard the girl.
- She's not coming with you.
- She is.
You're not
a good listener.
That Valyrian steel?
I always wanted
some Valyrian steel.
Come with me, Arya.
I'll take you to safety.
Safety?
Where the fuck's that?
Her aunt in the Eyrie is dead.
Her mother's dead.
Her father's dead.
Her brother's dead.
Winterfell is a pile
of rubble.
There is no safety,
you dumb bitch.
You don't know
that by now,
you're the wrong one
to watch over her.
And that's what
you're doing?
Watching over her?
Aye, that's what
I'm doing.
( grunts )
( panting )
I have no wish
to kill you, Ser.
I'm not a knight.
( grunts )
( groans )
( screams )
( screaming )
( groans )
( shouting )
( panting )
Arya!
- Where is she?
- Podrick: She was just here.
Why weren't you
watching her?
I was watching you.
I thought you might need some help.
Which way, Pod?
Which way did she go?
I think that way.
Brienne:
Arya!
( panting )
You still here?
( coughs )
Big bitch saved you.
I don't need saving.
No, not you.
You're a real killer.
With your water dancing
and your Needle.
You gonna die?
Unless there's a maester
hiding behind that rock,
aye,
I'm done.
I'd skin you alive
for wine.
Fuck water.
Killed by a woman.
( chuckles )
I bet you like that.
Go on,
go after her.
She'll help you.
Going it alone,
you won't last
a day out there.
I'll last
longer than you.
You remember where
the heart is?
Fuck it.
I'm ready.
Go on, girl.
Another name
off your list.
You kept
promising me.
I cut down
your butcher's boy.
The ginger.
He was begging
for mercy.
"Please, Ser.
Please don't kill me.
Please, please."
Bled all over
my horse.
Saddle stunk of butcher's boy
for weeks.
And your sister.
Your pretty sister.
I should have taken her.
That night
the Blackwater burned.
I should have
fucked her bloody.
At least I'd have
one happy memory.
Do I have to beg you?
Do it.
Kill me.
Kill me!
( door opens )
( door closes )
( footsteps )
Oh, get on with it,
you son of a whore.
Is that any way to speak
about our mother?
What are you doing?
What do you
think I'm doing?
A galley's waiting in the bay
bound for the Free Cities.
- Who's helping you?
- Varys.
- Varys?
- You have more friends than you thought.
There's a locked door
at the top of the stairs.
Knock on it twice,
then twice again.
Varys will open.
I suppose this
is good-bye, then.
Farewell, little brother.
Jaime.
Thank you for my life.
Quickly now.
Tywin?
My lion.
( grunting )
( choking )
( grunts )
( gasping )
( whimpers )
I'm sorry.
( exhales )
( crossbow lever dragging )
( door creaks )
Tyrion.
Put down the crossbow.
Who released you?
Your brother,
I expect.
He always had
a soft spot for you.
Come, we'll go and talk
in my chambers.
This is how you want
to speak to me, hmm?
Shaming your father has
always given you pleasure.
All my life
you've wanted me dead.
Yes.
But you refused to die.
I respect that.
Even admire it.
You fight
for what's yours.
I'd never let them
execute you.
Is that what you fear?
I'll never let Ilyn Payne
take your head.
You're a Lannister.
You're my son.
I loved her.
Who?
Shae.
Oh, Tyrion.
- Put down that crossbow.
- I murdered her.
With my own hands.
- It doesn't matter.
- Doesn't matter?
She was a whore.
- Say that word again...
- And what?
You'll kill your own
father in the privy?
No.
You're my son.
Now, enough
of this nonsense.
I am your son and you
sentenced me to die.
You knew I didn't
poison Joffrey,
but you sentenced me
all the same.
- Why?
- Enough.
We'll go back
to my chambers
and speak
with some dignity.
I can't go back there.
She's in there.
You're afraid
of a dead whore?
( groans )
You shot me.
You're no son of mine.
I am your son.
I have always
been your son.
( groans )
What have you done?
Quickly.
Trust me, my friend.
I brought you this far.
( bells tolling )
I want to see
the captain.
You're seeing him.
I want to go north
to the Wall.
No, you don't.
I can pay.
There is nothing in the North
but ice and war and pirates.
I wouldn't need a cabin.
Please.
I could work
scrubbing the floors.
I'm not going north, child.
I'm going home.
- Where's home?
- The Free City of Braavos.
Wait.
I have something else.
More silver won't make
a difference.
It's not silver.
It's iron.
This...
How did you--
Valar morghulis.
Valar dohaeris.
Of course,
you shall have a cabin.
== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
♪ Theme music playing  ♪
♪ Theme music ends  ♪