(theme music playing)
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
(men chatting)
Man:
Brace the wind.
The Lord of Light has made
good on his promise, my king.
His fires have melted
the snows away.
The way ahead is clear.
We ride for Winterfell.
And you will take it.
The Lord has shown me
Bolton banners burning.
You will receive
what is yours by right.
Your Grace.
Prepare to form up.
Tell me.
The men, many deserted
before dawn.
Stannis:
How many?
General:
Nearly half.
All the sellswords
with all the horses.
Your Grace.
Speak up. Can't be
worse than mutiny.
Cut her down.
General:
Your Grace.
The Lady Melisandre was just
seen riding out of camp.
Get the men
into marching formation.
On to Winterfell.
-  (distant horse neighs)
-  (wind howling)
He raised his hands
and they all stood up at once.
Tens of thousands of them.
The biggest army in the world.
So what are you gonna do?
I'm gonna hope they don't
learn how to climb the Wall.
But the dragonglass...
No one's ever
getting that back now.
It wouldn't have
mattered anyway.
Not unless we had
a mountain of it.
But you killed a white walker.
With Longclaw.
I saw them shatter steel
axes like they were glass.
- But Longclaw...
- Sam: Is Valyrian steel.
How many Valyrian steel swords
are left in the Seven Kingdoms?
Not enough.
The first Lord Commander
in history
to sacrifice the lives
of sworn brothers
to save the lives of wildlings.
How's it feel to be friends with the
most hated man in Castle Black?
You were friends with me
when I first came here.
And I wasn't winning
any elections back then.
Here's to us, then.
Long may they sneer.
What?
I wanted to ask you something.
To ask something of you.
Send me, Gilly,
and the baby to Oldtown
so I can become a maester.
That's what I'm meant to be.
Not this.
I need you here, Sam.
If you leave, who's left
to give me advice I trust?
Well, there's Edd.
I'd be more use
to you as a maester.
More use to everyone now
that Maester Aemon is gone.
The Citadel has the
world's greatest library.
I'll learn about history,
strategy, healing.
And other things,
things that will
help when--
when they come.
If Gilly stays here,
then she'll die.
And the baby that she
named after me will die.
And I'll end up dying, too,
trying to protect them.
Which means that the last thing
that I'll see in this world
will be the look in her
eyes when I fail them.
And I'd rather see a thousand
white walkers than see that.
(sighs)
Thank you.
You know that the Citadel will
make you swear off women, too.
Oh, they'll bloody try.
- Sam.
- What?
Sam.
You had just been beaten half to death.
How did you--
Oh, very carefully.
I'm glad the end of the world's
working out well for someone.
I'll come back.
To your return.
To my return.
(clicks)
Man:
Aye, this way.
(distant men shouting)
Podrick:
My lady!
Stannis.
Stannis Baratheon is coming.
His whole army.
How do you know it's Stannis?
They're carrying his
flaming heart banners.
From the Blackwater.
I'll never forget it.
(grunts)
Trench here.
Another one 300 yards
from the castle wall.
Hurry them along.
- Right, Curlew.
- Yes, sir.
Dig between those two rises.
- Spread out.
- Soldier: I'm with you.
- Soldier #2: Archers!
- Soldier #3: Spread out!
And send out a foraging
party immediately.
Siege begins at sunrise.
There's not going to be
a siege, Your Grace.
(horses neighing)
Soldier:
We've got no chance!
- (men shouting)
- (weapons clanging)
-  (weapons slicing)
-  (men screaming)
- (groaning)
-  (horse neighs)
(groans)
(grunting)
- Soldier:  No, please, please.
-  (sword pierces)
(all shouting)
(roars)
(groans)
(shouts)
(growls, sighs)
(footsteps approaching)
Bolton has women
fighting for him?
I don't fight for the Boltons.
I'm Brienne of Tarth.
I was Kingsguard
to Renly Baratheon.
I was there when he was murdered
by a shadow with your face.
You murdered him
with blood magic?
I did.
In the name of Renly
of House Baratheon,
First of His Name,
rightful King of the Andals
and the First Men,
Lord of the Seven Kingdoms
and Protector of the Realm,
I, Brienne of Tarth,
sentence you to die.
Do you have any last words?
Go on, do your duty.
Looks like we're done here.
(soldier groaning)
I surrender!
And I accept your surrender.
(groans)
Let's head back.
My wife must be lonely.
(bird screeching)
(men shouting)
(gasps)
My lady.
I've come to escort you
back to your chamber.
Go with her, please.
I know what Ramsay is.
I know what he'll do to me.
If I'm going to die,
let it happen while there's
still some of me left.
Die?
Who said anything about dying?
You can't die.
Your father was
Warden of the North.
Ramsay needs you.
Though I suppose he
doesn't need all of you.
Just the parts he'll use
to make his heir,
until you've given him a boy or
two and he's finished using them.
Then he's got incredible
plans for those parts.
So, shall we wait
for him to come back
or should we begin now?
You're leaving it to me?
Good.
Let's begin.
Reek-- stop!
Stop!
(screams)
(grunts)
-  (horn blows)
- Man: Open the gate!
He's coming back.
(shaky breathing)
(screams)
-  (whips)
- (whimpers)
(switch breaks)
I can see I have
my work cut out for me.
You two, out.
(door opens, closes)
(grunts)
(coughing, gasping)
(screams)
(screaming)
(grunting)
(groaning)
You were the first person
on my list, you know.
For killing Syrio Forel.
Remember him?
Probably not.
I've gotten a few of the others.
The Many-Faced God stole
a few more from me.
But I'm glad he left me you.
Do you know who I am?
(muffled)
I can't hear you.
-  (pierces)
- (groans)
(groans)
You know who I am.
I'm Arya Stark.
- (pierces)
- (groans)
Do you know who you are?
(whimpers)
You're no one.
You're nothing.
(gurgling)
A girl has taken a life.
The wrong life.
I was right about her.
You were.
You're not ready.
Not at all.
(gasps)
That man's life
was not yours to take.
A girl stole from
the Many-Faced God.
Now a debt is owed.
(whimpering)
Only death can pay for life.
(crying)
No! No!
No, you-- don't die!
Don't die!
Why are you crying?
He was my friend.
No, he wasn't.
Didn't you listen to him?
Jaqen:
He was no one.
(gasps)
But if you're--
who's this?
Jaqen:
No one at all.
Just as a girl should have been
before she took a face from the hall.
The faces are for no one.
You are still someone.
And to someone,
the faces are as good as poison.
(gasps)
(whimpering)
I can't see.
What's happening?
What's happening?!
(birds screeching)
- Doran: I wish you a safe journey home.
- Thank you.
Forgive me, child.
I wish you all the
happiness in the world.
Maybe I'll come
visit you sometime.
Maybe I'll come visit you.
Don't wait too long.
Got a noblewoman
to marry back home.
You want a good girl,
but you need the bad pussy.
Jaime: Whenever you're
ready, my lord.
(birds screeching)
Try not to lose it this time.
I'll never take it off again.
I know you didn't
want to leave Dorne,
but I'm glad you're coming home.
Your mother's desperate
to see you.
I'm glad Trystane
is coming with us.
He seems like a nice boy.
You're lucky.
Arranged marriages
are rarely so--
so well arranged.
Do you think Mother
will like him?
If she sees you're happy,
I'm sure she will.
(laughs)
You really believe that?
Have you ever known
your mother to like anyone
aside from her children?
She likes you.
I'm not so sure about that.
Listen...
there's something
I wanted to tell you.
Something I should
have told you long ago.
So...
now that you've seen
more of the world,
you've learned how
complicated things can be,
people can be.
The Lannisters and the Martells
have hated each other for years,
but you've fallen
in love with Trystane.
It was an accident, really.
I mean, what were the chances?
You happen to fall
in love with the man
you were assigned to marry?
My point is...
we don't choose whom we love.
It just, well--
it's beyond our control.
- I sound like an idiot.
- No, you don't.
What I'm trying to say--
what I'm trying
and failing to say--
I know what
you're trying to say.
No, I'm afraid you don't.
I do.
I know.
About you and Mother.
I think a part of me
always knew.
And I'm glad.
I'm glad that you're my father.
Myrcella?
(gasping)
(dragon screeches)
(knuckles cracking)
You love her, don't you?
How could you not?
Of course it's hopeless
for the both of you.
A sellsword from the fighting
pits, a disgraced knight.
Neither one of you is fit
consort for a queen.
But we always want
the wrong woman.
Does he always talk so much?
(footsteps)
Jorah the Andal.
Torgo Nudho.
He should not be here.
No, but he is.
Our queen ordered him
exiled from city.
Our queen would be dead
if not for him.
_
Puñila.
Thank you.
I am sorry.
Sorry I not there
to fight for our queen.
You missed a good scrap.
None of that matters now.
The longer we sit
here bantering,
the longer Daenerys is out
there in the wilderness.
He's right.
The dragon headed north.
If we're going to find her,
that's where we'll have to go.
We?
You're a Lannister.
The queen intends to remove
your family from power.
And I intend to help her do it.
You've been here
for how many days now?
I've fought for her for years.
Since she was little
more than a child.
- You betrayed her.
- Careful now.
And she exiled you.
Twice, I believe.
The second time thanks to you.
Don't blame me for
your crimes, Mormont.
He's right.
Our queen exiled Jorah.
And he's right.
Jorah saved her life.
Perhaps she feels
differently about him now.
Perhaps not. The only way
we'll know is if we ask her.
Tyrion: Fine, fine. I
suppose he can join us.
Just as long as he promises
not to kill me in my sleep.
If I ever kill you,
your eyes will be wide open.
Forgive me, but why
would we bring you?
Pardon me?
Have you ever tracked
animals in the wilderness?
Not precisely, but I have other
skills that would be useful.
Can you fight?
I have fought.
I don't claim to be
a great warrior.
Are you good on a horse?
Middling.
So mainly you talk.
And drink.
I've survived so far.
Which I respect, but you would
not help us on this expedition.
You would help us
here in Meereen, though.
None of us have experience
governing a city
except for him.
You want to prove
your value to the queen?
Prove it right here in Meereen.
He's a foreign dwarf that
barely speaks the language.
Why would the Meereenese
listen to him?
They wouldn't.
They will listen to Grey Worm.
I'll come with you.
I'll find our queen.
- You are not strong enough to go anywhere.
- I am.
He is. He's the toughest man
with no balls I ever met.
But you still can't go.
The people believe in you.
They know you speak
for the queen.
It's true.
Only the Unsullied can keep
the peace in Meereen.
If you leave, half this city
will consume the other half.
And Missandei.
Our queen trusts no one
more than Missandei.
Certainly not me.
The queen's closest confidante,
the commander of the Unsullied,
and a foreign dwarf
with a scarred face.
Good fortune, my friends.
Meereen is ancient and glorious.
Try not to ruin her.
Looks like it's you and me,
Jorah the Andal.
Let's find some good horses.
We have so much to talk about.
(dragon screeches)
(birds chirping)
Varys:
Hello, old friend.
I thought we were so happy
together until you abandoned me.
I suppose there's no point
asking how you found me.
The birds sing in the west,
the birds sing in the east,
if one knows how to listen.
They tell me you've
already found favor
with the Mother of Dragons.
Well, she didn't execute me,
so that's a promising start.
Now the heroes
are off to find her
and I'm stuck here
trying to placate a city
on the brink of civil war.
Any advice for an old comrade?
Information is the key.
You need to learn your enemy's
strengths and strategies.
You need to learn which of your
friends are not your friends.
If only I knew someone
with a vast network of spies.
If only.
A grand old city
choking on violence,
corruption, and deceit.
Who could possibly
have any experience
managing such a massive,
ungainly beast?
I did miss you.
Oh, I know.
(dragon growls)
We have to go home.
Oh, my poor, sweet thing.
Does it hurt?
We have to go home.
Drogon.
Can you take me back to Meereen?
How far did you carry me?
(groans)
Drogon, we need to return.
My people need me.
(hisses)
(growling)
(gasps)
Well, there's no food.
At the very least, you
could hunt us some supper.
(horse neighs)
(horse whinnies)
(horses neigh)
(men whooping)
(lock clicks)
(door opens)
(whimpers)
Confess.
I have sinned.
I see that now.
How can I have been
so blind for so long?
I want to be clean again.
I want absolution.
The Crone came to me
with her lamp raised high.
And by its holy light--
You wish to make a confession?
Once I've confessed,
will I be free?
Your Grace will be dealt
with according to her sins.
The Mother have mercy, then.
I lay with a man outside the
bonds of marriage. I confess.
Name him.
Lancel Lannister.
Your cousin
and the king's squire.
- I was lonely and afraid.
- You had a husband.
A husband off whoring
every chance he--
His sins do not pardon your own.
May the gods forgive me.
Other men?
No.
No others?
Speaking falsehoods before
the gods is a great crime.
You understand this?
I do.
There are those
that say your children
were not fathered
by King Robert,
that they are bastards
born of incest and adultery.
A lie.
A lie from the lips
of Stannis Baratheon.
He wants the throne, but his
brother's children stand in his way.
So he claims they are
not his brother's.
That filth.
There is not one shred
of truth to it.
I deny it.
Good.
But these are terrible charges.
And the realm must know
the truth of them.
If Your Grace has given
honest testimony,
your trial will prove
your innocence.
Trial?
I have confessed.
To a single sin.
Others you have denied.
Your trial will separate the
truths from the falsehoods.
I bow to the wisdom
of Your High Holiness.
But if I might beg
for just one drop
of the Mother's mercy.
I haven't seen my son--
I don't know how long it's been.
I need to see him, please.
You have taken the first step on
the path back to righteousness.
In light of this,
I will permit you
to return to the Red Keep.
Thank you.
(crying)
The Mother is merciful.
It is her you should thank.
I will. I will.
I swear it, day and night.
Good.
Am I free to go?
After your atonement.
My atonement?
(door opens)
A sinner comes before you.
Cersei of House Lannister.
Mother to His Grace King Tommen.
Widow of His Grace King Robert.
She has committed
the acts of falsehood
and fornication.
She has confessed her sins
and begged for forgiveness.
To demonstrate her repentance,
she will cast aside
all pride, all artifice,
and present herself
as the gods made her
to you,
the good people of the city.
She comes before you
with a solemn heart,
shorn of secrets,
naked before the eyes
of gods and men...
to make her walk of atonement.
Shame.
(bell rings)
Shame. Shame.
Shame.
(bell rings)
Shame. Shame.
- (crowd murmuring)
-  Shame. Shame.
- Shame.
- (bell rings)
Shame.
Shame. Shame.
(bell rings)
Shame.
- Cunt!
- Shame.
- Woman: Sinner!
- Woman #2: Whore!
- Shame.
- Woman #3: Whore!
- (bell rings)
- Shame.
- Whore! Whore!
-  Shame.
(crowd shouting)
-  (bell rings)
-  Shame.
Shame.
(overlapping voices)
Whore! Sinner!
- Shame.
- Bitch! Brother fucker!
- Whore!
- Shame.
- Fuck off!
- (bell rings)
- Shame.
- All hail the royal tits.
- Man: You're a bitch!
- Shame.
- (bell rings)
- Get her!
- Whore!
- Bitch!
- Fucker!
- You bitch!
-  Shame.
- Cunt!
-  (bell rings)
- Shame. Shame.
- (shouting continues)
- Brother fucker!
- Bitch!
I've had half as many
cocks as the queen.
- Bitch!
- Shame.
- (overlapping voices) Sinner! Whore! Slut!
(laughter, shouting continues)
- (bell rings)
- Shame.
(booing)
Shame. Shame.
- Whore!
- Whore, whore.
I'm a Lannister.
Suck me off!
- Suck me off, you bitch!
- Back!
- Whore!
- Shame.
- (bell rings)
- (laughing)
- Crowd: Whore!
Crowd:
Whore! Whore! Whore!
- (woman cackling)
-  Shame. Shame.
- Shame.
- (bell rings)
- (crowd shouting)
-  Shame.
- Shame.
- (bell rings)
Shame.
- Man: Bitch! Bitch!
- Unella: Shame.
(shouting continues)
Brother fucker!
- Unella: Shame. Shame.
- (bell rings)
- (shouting continues)
- Shame.
- Man: Whore!
- Man #2: Brother fucker!
- Man #3: Whore!
- Shame.
Shame.
(bell rings)
- (crowd jeering)
- Shame.
- (bell rings)
Shame.
- Shame.
-  (bell rings)
-  Shame.
- Man: Fucker!
(bell rings)
Shame. Shame.
- (whimpers)
- Shame.
Shame.
- (shouting)
-  Shame. Shame.
- Shame.
- (bell rings)
Shame. Shame.
- Shame.
- (bell rings)
Shame.
(shouting continues)
- Shame. Shame.
- (bell rings)
Shame. Shame.
Shame.
(crying)
(shouting continues)
(door closes)
(crying)
Your Grace.
(sobbing)
It's good to have you back.
Come.
We'll take you inside.
I need to have a look
at those feet.
-  (footsteps)
-  (armor clanking)
May I have the honor of presenting
the newest member of the Kingsguard?
If it please Your Grace, he has
taken a holy vow of silence.
He has sworn
that he will not speak
until all His Grace's
enemies are dead
and evil has been
driven from the realm.
Who came to your aid?
Stannis.
Now he needs you.
We don't have enough men
to make any difference.
The wildlings will make
a difference.
The wildlings will never
fight for Stannis.
- I told him before.
- You saved their bloody lives.
If they're gonna live
in the Seven Kingdoms,
safe behind our Wall, they ought
to fight for the damn place.
- It's not their fight.
- Man: Open the gates!
Stannis?
Shireen?
The princess?
Lord Commander.
It's one of the wildlings
you brought back.
Says he knows your Uncle Benjen.
Says he's still alive.
Are you sure he's
talking about Benjen?
Said he was First Ranger.
Said he knows where to find him.
Man says he saw
your uncle at Hardhome
at the last full moon.
- Could be lying.
- Could be.
There are ways to find out.
- Where is he?
- Over there.
(groans)
For the Watch.
(gasping)
- (groans)
- For the Watch.
(labored breathing)
(wheezing)
Olly...
(groans)
For the Watch.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com