A royal wedding is history.
He's choking!
Joffrey!
- Come with me now.
- Joffrey!
He poisoned my son.
Take him.
Take him!
You're safe with me
and sailing home.
They say 1,000 slaves died
building the Great
Pyramid of Meereen.
Your brother is dead.
Do you know what that means?
It means I'll become king.
Yes.
Now, as the king,
you will have to marry.
I demand
a trial by combat.
Tyrion Lannister,
you are hereby
sentenced to death.
He came from the sky.
My girl.
My little girl.
Myrcella is my only daughter.
Dorne is the safest place
for her.
You're Arya Stark.
I'll take you to safety.
Arya!
Ser Lancel, Cersei must have
great trust in you.
Get back to bed.
More wine, Your Grace?
A boar got me.
100 generations
have defended this castle.
She will not fall tonight.
Let's kill some crows!
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com
- We shouldn't be out here alone.
- Why not?
- If your father--
- He'll never know we're gone.
But if he finds out...
You don't need
to be afraid of my father.
Are you sure?
Yes.
- We shouldn't go in.
- Of course we should.
Get out.
Get out!
- Let's go.
- No.
Listen to your friend.
They said that you
were terrifying
with cat's teeth and three eyes.
You're not terrifying.
You're boring.
You don't know what I am.
I know you're a witch
and you can see the future.
Tell me mine.
Everyone wants
to know their future
until they know their future.
This is my father's land.
My land.
Tell me my future or I'll have your two
boring eyes gouged out of your head.
Your blood.
Give me a taste.
Three questions you get.
You won't like the answers.
I've been promised
to the prince.
When will we marry?
You will never wed the prince.
You will wed the king.
But I will be queen?
Oh, yes.
You'll be queen.
For a time.
Then comes another,
younger,
more beautiful,
to cast you down
and take all you hold dear.
W-will the king and I
have children?
No. The king will have 20
children and you will have three.
That doesn't make sense.
Gold will be their crowns.
Gold their shrouds.
Come on, we have to go.
We have to go!
Cersei!
Bearers, put it down.
Bearers, up.
Away.
Your Grace, we are
honored by your presence.
The mourners are waiting.
They will keep waiting.
I want a moment alone with him.
But, Your Grace, many of these lords
and ladies have travelled
day and night to be here from
all seven kingdoms.
They will wait.
He never wanted you
to be a Kingsguard,
but here you are,
protecting his dead body.
What he built, it's ours.
He built it for us.
He meant it for us.
They're going to try
to take it away.
- All of it.
- They?
All of them out there,
our enemies.
They're waiting in line to make sure
he's really dead.
And as soon as they see
the stones on his eyes,
they'll set to work
on tearing us apart.
They have nothing to do with it.
The man who murdered our father,
he tore us apart.
He's the enemy.
I've been telling you for years.
You've been defending
him for years.
This is exactly what they want.
And now our father is dead
and that little monster
is out there somewhere drawing breath.
Did you set him free?
Tyrion may be a monster,
but at least he killed
our father on purpose.
You killed him by mistake.
With stupidity.
You're a man
of action, aren't you?
When it occurs to you
to do something, you do it.
Never mind the consequences.
Take a look.
Look at the consequences.
Here they are.
He loved you more than
anyone in this world.
Apologies.
I still don't see
why I had to stay
in this fucking crate
once we set sail.
I saved your life.
If they catch you,
they catch me.
I cannot say
I feel overly guilty
about leaving you
in that fucking crate.
Do you know what it's like
to stuff your shit
through one of those airholes?
No, I only know what it's like
to pick up your shit
and throw it overboard.
Pentos?
The home of my colleague
Illyrio Mopatis,
a merchant.
He and I met many years ago
through mutual friends.
A group of people
who saw Robert Baratheon
for the disaster he was.
We tried to do what
was best for the realm
by supporting
a Targaryen restoration.
And thus began
the chain of mistakes
that has led us both here.
Things have gotten worse,
not better.
Westeros needs to be
saved from itself.
Mmm.
Much better.
My lord?
I don't think I am anymore.
A lord.
Are you a lord
if you kill your father?
I don't imagine
they revoke your nobility
for killing a whore.
It must happen all the time.
You already drank yourself
across the Narrow Sea.
In a box.
Why stop now?
Because we are talking
about the future of our country.
The future is shit.
Just like the past.
_
Shh.
The Sons of the Harpy?
Yes, Your Grace.
They left it on the body.
They've never killed before.
It was only a matter
of time, Your Grace.
Conquerors always meet
with resistance.
I didn't conquer them.
Their own people did.
_
He did not risk his life
fighting for his freedom
so cowards in masks
could take it away.
And I did not take up
residence in this pyramid
so I could watch the city below
decline into chaos.
What was the name
of the man you lost?
White Rat, Your Grace.
I want him buried
with honor, publically
in the Temple of the Graces.
The Sons of the Harpy
will hear that message.
Make them very angry.
Angry snakes lash out.
Makes chopping off their heads
that much easier.
Find the men who did this
and bring them to me.
Your Grace.
Torgo Nudho.
Missandei hin Naath.
I wanted to speak with you.
Why do you come?
White Rat, the Unsullied who...
I have heard they found
his body in a brothel.
I have heard that
more than one Unsullied
has been known to visit
Meereen's brothels.
May I ask you why?
Why would an Unsullied
go to a brothel?
I do not know.
I must go.
- Get your shield up.
- It's too heavy.
If it wasn't heavy,
it wouldn't stop a sword.
Now get it up.
Come.
Try it again.
Drive at me.
Keep your shield up.
Or I'll ring
your head like a bell.
Shouldn't you be training, too?
Well, I'm hardly a new recruit.
How many brothers can say that they've
killed a white walker and a Thenn?
I might be the first in history.
- Shield up.
- These men need a firm hand.
Always have.
They're poachers and thieves.
Not soldiers.
That one hates me.
If Ser Alliser
is chosen as the new Lord Commander...
He hates the wildlings.
All the wildlings.
- Don't let them send us away.
-  It's not a sure thing.
Ser Denys Mallister has
commanded the Shadow Tower for 20 years
and people say he's a good man.
He's running against
Ser Alliser--
Sam, don't let them
send us away.
I told you.
Wherever you go, I go, too.
You can't leave.
They'll execute you.
- Good, good, pivot. Don't forget to pivot.
- Yah!
Shield up.
The king wants a word.
You're not cold, my lady?
Never.
The Lord's fire lives
within me, Jon Snow.
Feel.
Are you a virgin?
No.
Good.
Your Grace.
The bastard of Winterfell.
You know who rules
at Winterfell now?
Roose Bolton.
Mmm, the traitor who plunged a dagger
in Robb Stark's heart.
Don't you want to avenge him?
I want a great
many things, Your Grace.
But I'm a sworn brother
of the Night's Watch now.
I've been talking
to your sworn brothers.
- Many of them love you.
- They're good men.
Many don't.
You were seen taking the body
of a wildling girl north of the Wall.
Why?
It's where she belonged.
Some of the Night's
Watch feel you have
too much affection
for the wildlings.
They were born on the
wrong side of the Wall.
That doesn't make them monsters.
No matter.
I shall take back the North
from the thieves who stole it.
Tywin Lannister is dead.
He can't protect them now.
I shall mount Roose Bolton's
head on a spike.
But if I'm to take Winterfell,
I need more men.
The men of the Night's Watch
are sworn to play no part--
I'm not talking about
the damn Night's Watch.
I'm talking about the wildlings.
Your Grace,
you want the wildlings
to march in your army?
If they swear to follow me,
I'll pardon them.
We'll take Winterfell.
Once the North is won,
I'll declare them
citizens of the realm.
I'll give them land to live on.
It's a fair offer.
More than fair.
I'll offer them their lives
and their freedom
if Mance kneels before me
and swears his loyalty.
I don't think that's likely.
You admire him, don't you?
- I respect him.
- He likes you.
- Convince him to bend the knee...
- Your Grace.
...or he burns.
How much time do I have?
Nightfall.
The sun drops fast
this time of year.
Hurry, Jon Snow.
Shield up.
Attack, my lord!
Attack!
Don't cross your feet.
My sons had swords
in their hands
from the time they could walk.
This one...
Lord Arryn will never
be a great warrior.
Great warrior?
He swings a sword
like a girl with palsy.
My lord.
Sword up, my lord!
Some boys develop more slowly.
He's still young.
He's 13.
Boys go to war at 13.
- He has other gifts.
- Does he?
The gift of a great name.
Sometimes that's all one needs.
Good-bye, Lord Royce, and thank you
for all you've done for me.
I have done nothing more
than my duty, my lady.
I have no doubt
that on my return,
Robin's skills will have
improved immeasurably.
He'll be safe here.
As for his skills,
I make no promises.
Will we head north
at some point?
He said Sansa had a brother
at Castle Black.
We're a few days' ride
from the Kingsroad.
- But that will take us--
- Us?
The only reason you're here
is because Jaime Lannister
told me you weren't
safe in the capital.
You're hundreds of miles
from King's Landing.
No one knows what you look like.
No one cares.
You're safe.
- But I'm your squire.
- Do you even know what a squire is?
An attendant to a knight.
I'm not a knight.
That means you're not a squire.
Well, where would I go?
I don't care.
I'm not your mother.
You swore to find
the Stark girls.
I found Arya. She didn't want
my protection.
-  Sansa still might.
- Will you shut your mouth?
I didn't ask for your advice.
I don't want anyone
following me.
I'm not a leader.
All I ever wanted
was to fight for a lord I believed in.
The good lords are dead
and the rest are monsters.
You told Lord Royce
we were going to the Fingers.
I did.
- But we're heading west.
- We are.
If he wanted to betray us,
he already would have.
Lord Royce might be as honorable
as he thinks he is,
but he's not alone
in that castle.
Do you trust all those
knights and ladies,
stable boys and serving girls?
No, do you trust the carriage driver
or the knights escorting us?
No.
But I pay them well
and they've seen what happens
to men who disappoint me.
So where are we going?
To a land where
you trust everyone?
To a land so far from here,
even Cersei Lannister
can't get her hands on you.
It was such a deep,
deep shock to us all.
Your father was a--
a force to be reckoned with.
He truly was.
I wouldn't presume to claim
to have known him
as such, but--
but just being in his presence was enough
to make it so clear
just how formidable
a person you were dealing with.
What a-- what a force
to be reckoned with.
Thank you so much
for your kind words.
Deepest condolences, Your Grace.
This tragedy...
I never trusted Varys.
I often warned...
Your Grace.
Cousin Lancel.
I hardly recognized you.
My deepest sympathies.
I apologize
for my son's appearance.
Uncle, it's quite all right.
They call themselves sparrows.
Bloody fanatics.
Religion has its place,
of course,
but at a certain point...
They never would have come to the capital
when Tywin was alive.
I'm sure he'll grow out of it,
whatever it is.
- Excuse me.
- Of course.
Your wounds from the Blackwater
seem to have healed.
It wasn't my wounds
that needed healing.
What can I do for you?
You can forgive me.
What could you possibly
have done to warrant my forgiveness?
I led you into the darkness.
I doubt you've ever
led anyone anywhere.
I tempted you into our...
unnatural relations.
And, of course,
there was the king...
his boar hunt.
His wine.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
I'm a different person now.
I've found peace
in the light of the Seven.
You can, too.
They watch over all of us,
ready to dole out mercy
or justice.
Their world is at hand.
I will pray for
your father's soul.
The day Tywin Lannister's
soul needs your help...
- It looks like Dorne.
- It doesn't.
It does.
That's the--
that's the Sunspear bit right there.
And that's where
the mountains are.
And over here is--
is Sunsnake?
Stonespear?
Sandstone.
Yes.
Yes, Sandstone.
Just there.
Fine.
It's Dorne.
We should go there.
I think we would
have a lovely time,
judging by my experience.
That would be wonderful.
Dorne, Highgarden.
Anywhere but here.
We're late for dinner as it is.
You're very respectful.
I'm very hungry.
What's your name?
Olyvar, my lady.
I'm afraid my brother
is keeping the king
waiting, Olyvar.
My lady.
Perhaps you might
consider being a bit more discreet?
Why?
They all know about me anyway.
Everybody knows everything
about everyone.
What's the point in trying to
keep a secret in a place like this?
In any event, you shouldn't
keep your intended waiting.
My intended?
Please.
Tywin's dead.
That means no one
can force Cersei to marry me.
- Lucky you.
- Unlucky you.
You think I want that woman
married to my brother?
If she doesn't marry me,
she doesn't go to Highgarden.
Which means she stays
in King's Landing.
Which means you're trapped here with
Cersei Lannister as your mother by law.
Perhaps.
Perhaps?
Eunuch, the Spider, the
Master of Whisperers.
Imp, Half-man.
There are faster ways
to kill yourself.
Not for a coward.
You are many things, my friend,
but not a coward.
You never told me
why you set me free.
Your brother asked me to.
Could have said no.
Refuse the Kingslayer?
A dangerous proposition.
Not as dangerous
as releasing me.
You risked your life,
your position, everything.
Why? You're not family.
You owe me nothing.
I didn't do it for you.
I did it for the Seven Kingdoms.
A drunken dwarf will never be the savior
of the Seven Kingdoms.
I don't believe in saviors.
I believe men of talent
have a part to play in the war to come.
You're going to have
to find another soldier.
I'm done with Westeros
and Westeros is done with me.
You have many
admirable qualities,
self-pity is not
one of them.
Any fool with a bit of luck
can find himself
born into power.
But earning it for yourself,
that takes work.
I'm not well-suited
for work.
I think you are.
You have your father's
instincts for politics.
And you have compassion.
Compassion? Yes.
I killed my lover
with my bare hands.
I shot my own father
with a crossbow.
I never said you were perfect.
What is it you want exactly?
Peace.
Prosperity.
A land where the powerful
do not prey on the powerless.
Where the castles
are made of gingerbread
and the moats are filled
with blackberry wine.
The powerful have always
preyed on the powerless.
That's how they became powerful
in the first place.
Perhaps.
And perhaps we've grown
so used to horror,
we assume there's no other way.
If you sat on the Iron Throne,
would you spread misery
throughout the land?
I will never sit
on the Iron Throne.
No, you won't.
But you could help another
climb those steps
and take that seat.
The Seven Kingdoms
need someone stronger than Tommen,
but gentler than Stannis.
A monarch who can intimidate the
high lords and inspire the people.
A ruler loved by millions
with a powerful army
and the right family name.
Good luck finding him.
Who said anything about "him"?
You have a choice, my friend.
You can stay here
at Illyrio's palace
and drink yourself to death,
or you can ride with me
to Meereen,
meet Daenerys Targaryen,
and decide if the world
is worth fighting for.
Can I drink myself to death
on the road to Meereen?
When did the Unsullied
start patrolling the streets of Meereen?
Looks like your friends haven't
been behaving themselves.
Our mission to Yunkai
was a resounding success.
The Wise Masters of Yunkai
have agreed to cede power
to a council of elders
made up of both
the freed men and
the former slaveholders.
All matters of consequence will be
brought to you for review.
Good.
They did ask
for some concessions.
Concessions?
Politics is the art
of compromise, Your Grace.
I'm not a politician.
I'm a queen.
Forgive me.
You're right, of course.
Still, it's easier to rule happy
subjects than angry ones.
I don't expect
the Wise Masters to be happy.
Slavery made them rich.
I ended slavery.
They do not ask
for the return of slavery.
They ask for the reopening
of the fighting pits.
The fighting pits?
Where slaves fought
slaves to the death?
In the new world
that you've brought to us,
free men would fight free men.
The pit fighters you liberated
plead for this opportunity.
Bring some here
and ask them yourself.
No fighting pits.
Opening them would show
the people of Yunkai
and Meereen that you
respect their traditions.
I do not respect the tradition of
human cockfighting.
If you-- - How many times must I say no
before you understand?
Whatever he wants from me,
he's not going to get it.
If he really believes
I'm going to reopen the fighting pits...
You should reopen
the fighting pits.
What?
My mother was a whore.
I told you that.
She liked to drink pear brandy.
The older she got, the less
she made selling her body,
the more she wanted to drink.
So one day when I was 12,
she sold me to a slaver
she fucked the night before.
I'm sorry.
Why?
I was a bad child.
I wasn't big, but I was quick.
And I loved to fight.
So they sold me
to a man in Tolos
who trained fighters
for the pits.
I had my first match
when I was 16.
You were sold into slavery,
forced to fight to the death
for the amusement of the masters,
and you're defending
the fighting pits?
I'm only here
because of those pits.
I learned to fight
like a Dothraki screamer,
a Norvoshi priest,
a Westerosi knight.
Soon I was famous.
10,000 men and women
screamed my name
when I stepped into the pit.
I made so much money
for my master,
he set me free when he died.
I joined the Second Sons.
And then I met you.
You're the queen.
Everyone's too afraid
of you to speak truth.
Everyone but me.
You've made thousands
of enemies all across the world.
As soon as they see weakness,
they'll attack.
Show your strength here, now.
That's why I have the Unsullied
patrolling the streets.
Anyone with a chest
full of gold can buy an army of Unsullied.
You're not
the Mother of Unsullied.
You're the Mother of Dragons.
I don't want another child's bones
dropped at my feet.
No one's seen Drogon in weeks.
For all I know, he's flown halfway
across the world.
I can't control them anymore.
A dragon queen with no dragons
is not a queen.
Viserion?
Rhaegal?
Easy. Easy.
Easy.
So here we are.
Here we are.
When we first met,
you were my prisoner.
And now, for our last meeting...
This doesn't have to be
our last meeting.
No, but it will be.
You know what Stannis wants?
He wants me to bend the knee.
And he wants the free folk
to fight for him.
I'll give him this much,
he's bold.
Shouldn't a king be bold?
Oh, aye.
I respect him.
If he gets what he wants,
I expect he'll be a better ruler
than the fools
sitting on the Iron Throne
the last hundred years.
But I'll never serve him.
You told me you weren't
here to conquer.
You told me your people
have bled enough.
That's right.
I don't want them bleeding for
Stannis Baratheon either.
You spent your life convincing
90 clans to come together
for the first time in history.
Thenns and Hornfoots,
the ice-river clans,
even the giants.
A life's work uniting them.
You didn't do it for power.
You didn't do it for glory.
You brought them
together to save them
because none of them
will survive the winter,
not if they're north
of the Wall.
Isn't their survival
more important than your pride?
Pride?
Fuck my pride.
This isn't about that.
Then bend the knee
and save your people.
They followed me
because they respected me.
Because they believed in me.
The moment I kneel
for a southern king, that's all gone.
And how many tens of thousands
are out there right now?
How many women?
How many children?
And you won't go out and rescue
them because why?
You're afraid of looking afraid.
Oh, I am afraid.
No shame in that.
How will they do it?
Beheading?
Hanging?
They'll burn you alive.
Bad way to go.
I'll be honest with you.
I don't want to die.
And burnt to death,
I don't want people
to remember me like that,
scorched and screaming.
But it's better than betraying
everything I believe.
And what happens to your people?
You preserve your dignity
and die standing
and they'll sing
songs about you.
You'd rather burn than kneel.
The great hero.
Until winter comes and
the white walkers come for us all
and there's no one left to sing.
You're a good lad.
Truly you are.
But if you can't understand why I won't
enlist my people
in a foreigner's war,
there's no point explaining.
I think you're making
a terrible mistake.
The freedom to make
my own mistakes
was all I ever wanted.
Mance Rayder, you've been called
the King-beyond-the-Wall.
Westeros only has one king.
Bend the knee,
I promise you mercy.
Kneel and live.
This was my home for many years.
I wish you good fortune
in the wars to come.
We all must choose.
Man or woman, young or old,
lord or peasant,
our choices are the same.
We choose light
or we choose darkness.
We choose good
or we choose evil.
We choose the true god
or the false.
Free folk,
there is only one true king
and his name is Stannis.
Here stands your king of lies.
Behold the fate of those
who choose the darkness.
Sync & corrections by honeybunny
www.addic7ed.com