- The Kingslayer, he escaped in the night.
- How?!
Sansa and Arya are captives
in King's Landing.
Returning him may buy life
for my children.
Ser Barristan Selmy, it is
time to put aside your sword.
You're too old
to protect anyone.
Even now I could cut through the
5 of you like carving a cake.
Here, boy.
Melt it down and add it
to the others.
Where are my dragons?!
I will take you
to the House of the Undying
where I have put them.
Walder Frey is a
dangerous man to cross.
I love her.
The Iron Throne is mine.
No one wants you
for their king.
Look to your sins, Lord Renly.
The night is dark
and full of terrors.
If Renly wasn't a king,
I wasn't a queen.
- Do you want to be a queen?
- I want to be the queen.
Mance is gonna
march on the Wall.
One brother inside his army
will be worth 1,000
fighting against it.
- They'll never trust me.
- They might...
if you do what needs
to be done.
Come along, Jon Snow.
Time to meet
the King-beyond-the-Wall.
Welcome home,
Daenerys Stormborn.
Dracarys.
When I sit the Iron Throne,
you'll be my Hand.
I pray I serve you well.
I expect you'll be the first
crabber's son to wear the badge.
The battle is over.
We have won.
Ser Mandon Moore tried to kill
you on your sister's orders.
If it weren't for your squire's
bravery you'd be a dead man.
Ser Loras Tyrell, I will
gladly wed your sweet sister.
You said you saw
my victory in the flames.
This war has just begun.
You will be king.
It's Jon and the Halfhand.
Two blasts is wildlings.
Run!
Fall back!
Brother?
Did you send the ravens?
Tarly, look at me.
That was your job.
Your only job.
We need to get
back to the Wall.
It's a long march.
We know what's out there,
but we have to make it,
have to warn them
or before winter's done,
everyone you've ever known
will be dead.
First time you've seen
a giant, Jon Snow?
Well, don't stare too long.
They're shy.
When they stop being shy,
they get angry.
And when they're angry,
I've seen them pound a man
straight into the ground
like a hammer on a nail.
- Crow!
- Look over there!
Crow! Look over here!
Look!
Ah, look, crow coming!
Crow!
You're wearing
the wrong color.
Mance was a ranger.
In your hearts, all you
crows want to fly free.
When I'm free,
will I be free to go?
- Crow!
Sure, you will.
Oh!
And I'll be free to kill you.
Got no respect, this lot.
Got no fathers to slap 'em
when they're foul.
What happened to their fathers?
Some of them were killed
by crows like you.
Don't look so grim, Jon Snow.
If Mance Rayder likes you,
you'll live another day.
And if he don't...
I smell a crow.
We killed his friends.
Thought you'd want
to question this one.
What do we want
with a baby crow?
This baby killed
Qhorin Halfhand.
He wants to be one of us.
That half-handed cunt
killed friends of mine.
Friends twice your size.
My father told me big men fall
just as quick as little ones
if you put a sword
through their hearts.
Plenty of little men
tried to put their swords
through my heart.
And there's plenty
of little skeletons
buried in the woods.
- What's your name, boy?
- Jon Snow.
Your Grace.
Your Grace?
Did you hear that?
From now on, you'd better
kneel every time I fart.
Stand, boy.
We don't kneel for anyone
beyond the Wall.
So, you're Ned Stark's bastard.
Thank you for the gift,
Lord of Bones.
You can leave us.
The girl likes you.
You like her back, Snow?
That why you want to join us?
Don't panic, boy.
This isn't the damned
Night's Watch
where we make you
swear off girls.
This chicken eater you thought
was king is Tormund Giantsbane.
Can't believe this pup
killed the Halfhand.
He was our enemy
and I'm glad he's dead.
He was my brother once.
Back when he had a whole hand.
What were you doing with him?
The Lord Commander sent me
to the Halfhand for seasoning.
Why?
He wants me to lead one day.
But here you are, a traitor
kneeling before
the King-beyond-the-Wall.
If I'm a traitor,
then you are, too.
Why do you want
to join us, Jon Snow?
I want to be free.
No, I don't think so.
I think what you want
most of all
is to be a hero.
I'll ask you
one last time--
why do you want to join us?
We stopped at Craster's
Keep on the way north.
I saw...
You saw what?
I saw Craster take
his own baby boy
and leave it in the woods.
I saw what took it.
You're telling me
you saw one of them?
And why would that make you
desert your brothers?
Because when I told
the Lord Commander,
he already knew.
Thousands of years ago,
the First Men
battled the White Walkers
and defeated them.
I want to fight for the side
that fights for the living.
Did I come to the right place?
We'll need to find you
a new cloak.
What if you took off
that bit there?
Don't you want to leave
something to the imagination?
Trouble is, I've never
had much imagination.
I want you to take it off.
Mouth.
Ser Bronn. Ser Bronn.
I didn't hear that.
- Apologies, ser.
- Back away.
Keep backing away till you're
outside this establishment.
- Then back away some more.
- Lord Tyrion sent me.
I will murder you, boy.
He said it was a matter
of life and death.
- Pod?
- It's your sister.
The queen.
What are they doing here?
Protecting me, I assume.
Will you let me in?
No, I don't think so.
If I wanted to kill you,
do you think
I'd let a wooden door stop me?
They stay outside.
I'm not afraid of you,
little brother.
- Why are you here?
- I wanted to see your face.
They said you'd lost your nose, but
it's not as gruesome as all that.
The man who cut me
lost more than his nose.
I should hope so.
The rebels came for Joffrey's
head, they lost their own.
Thanks to Father.
Of course, it wasn't a rebel
who tried to kill me.
No? Curious.
Bit of a comedown
from chamber of the Hand.
But then I don't suppose
you need much room.
Grand Maester Pycelle
made the same joke.
You must be proud to be as funny as
a man whose balls brush his knees.
You're meeting Father today?
How do you know that?
Because I have hundreds
of spies in my employ.
The Master of Whisperers
owes me a favor or two.
Father told me.
What do you want from him?
What do I want from him?
He's my father.
Do I need to want something?
I'm sure he loves me dearly,
as any father loves his child,
his baby boy.
Yet he hasn't come
to visit once
since arriving
in King's Landing.
I lay here,
my face split in half,
but Father never came.
You're going to make me cry.
Why do you care
what I want from him?
Because you've slandered me
to Father before.
Slandered?
When?
You told him I had my guards
beat that servant girl
at Casterly Rock.
You did have
your guards beat her.
A girl of 9, I believe.
I was 9, too.
She lost an eye,
if I remember correctly.
If I remember correctly,
she never stole
a necklace again.
It's not slander if it's true.
And what's this truth
you plan on telling him today?
Why are you so nervous
about what I'm going
to say to Father?
Because you're a liar.
I expect you'll tell lies
about me, about Joffrey.
Any lies in particular?
You're a clever man,
but you're not half as clever
as you think you are.
Still makes me
more clever than you.
Oh, look at these two
shining warriors.
Ser Taryn Mant and...
Ser Whosit of Whocares.
Ser Meryn Trant.
Ser Bronn of the Blackwater.
- You're no knight.
- Pod.
Ser Bronn of the Blackwater
was anointed
by the king himself.
You're an up-jumped
cutthroat,
nothing more.
That's exactly who I am.
And you're a grub
in fancy armor
who's better at beating little
girls than fighting men.
Now, I have an appointment
with Lord Tyrion.
You put your hand on that door,
you lose the hand.
As much as I appreciate a walk
in the sunshine, your lordship,
I am wondering
why you sent for me.
A number of people
in this city want to kill me.
You're here to protect me.
I've been doing that
for a while now.
Do you grow bored
protecting me?
I grow poor protecting you.
Poor?
Under my patronage
you've become a knight,
you've served as Commander
of the City Watch.
- Briefly.
- I'm sure you filled your pockets.
And now my pockets are empty.
You've given me a taste
for the finer things.
And if you want me
to carry on protecting you,
you'll need to pay more.
- I thought we were friends.
- We are.
But I'm a sellsword.
I sell my sword.
I don't loan it out
to friends as a favor.
- How much?
- Double.
- Double?
- I'm a knight now.
Knights are worth double.
I don't even know how much
I'm paying you now.
Which means you can afford it.
Here. Here!
Help me!
Who are you?
I was in the battle
at Blackwater.
I was a captain and a knight.
Aye, ser,
and serving which king?
The one true king
of Westeros--
Stannis Baratheon.
I thought you were dead.
Everyone thought you were dead.
And your son?
He may have swam
ashore as you did.
No, the wildfire took him.
I saw it.
I'm so sorry, my friend.
I, too, have lost a son.
There is nothing worse
in this world.
But, Davos, you were
a good father.
If I was a good father,
he'd still be here.
Stannis lives?
He licks his wounds
at Dragonstone.
Will you take me there?
There is nothing for me
at Dragonstone.
This war is not over.
Not for you, maybe.
But for Salladhor Saan,
the war is over.
We're both sworn
to King Stannis.
I am sworn to no man.
I promised you 30 ships and you
promised me riches and glory.
I delivered the ships.
Stannis never gives up.
Never.
- Now he will regroup--
- He's a broken man.
His fleet lies at the bottom
of Blackwater Bay.
They say he sees no one--
not his generals,
not even his wife.
Only the Red Woman
whispering in his ear,
telling him what
she sees in the flames
and burning men alive.
What?
They built a great fire
when Stannis returned.
All those who spoke
against her she called
servants of darkness.
They say she sang
to them as they burned.
I'm a pirate.
You're a smuggler.
Servants of darkness.
I'm thinking Dragonstone is a
good place for us to avoid.
Take me back there, please.
You cannot turn
Stannis against her.
Maybe not, but I could
carve her heart out.
You could try.
If you fail,
they will burn you.
If you succeed,
they'll burn you.
And you've only
just come back to life.
Stay alive a little
longer, my friend.
You call me friend. You drank
with me on my wedding day.
And you drank with me
on 4 of my wedding days,
but I don't ask you for favors.
I have to stop her.
Please, do this for me.
When you are dead,
I will gather your bones
in a little sack
and let your widow
wear them around her neck.
We should set the siege lines
1,000 yards from Harrenhal.
There won't be a siege. The
Mountain can't defend a ruin.
I imagine the Mountain
will defend
whatever Tywin Lannister
tells him to defend.
The Lannisters have been
running from us since Oxcross.
I'd love a fight.
The men would love a fight.
I don't think
we're going to get one.
200 Northmen
slaughtered like sheep.
The debt will be
repaid, my friend.
For them and for your sons.
Will it?
They rot in the ground
while their killer runs free.
The Kingslayer won't
remain free for long.
My best hunters are after him.
- A Mallister?
- Ser Jeremy.
My father's bannerman.
Find her a chamber
that will serve as a cell.
She's your mother.
She freed Jaime Lannister.
The Lannisters robbed
them of their sons
and she robbed them
of their justice.
Water.
This needs to be
cleaned and closed.
What's your name, friend?
Qyburn.
You're lucky to be alive.
Lucky?
The badge looks good on you.
Almost as good
as it looked on me.
Are you enjoying
your new position?
Am I enjoying it?
I was very happy
as Hand of the King.
Yes.
I heard how happy you were.
You brought a whore
into my bed.
It wasn't your bed at the time.
I sent you here
to advise the king.
I gave you real power
and authority.
You chose to spend your days
as you always have,
bedding harlots
and drinking with thieves.
Occasionally I drank
with the harlots.
What do you want, Tyrion?
Why does everyone assume
I want something?
Can't I simply visit
with my beloved father?
My beloved father who
somehow forgot to visit
his wounded son
after he fell
on the battlefield.
Maester Pycelle assured me
your wounds were not fatal.
I organized
the defense of this city
while you held court
in the ruins of Harrenhal.
I led the foray when the
enemies were at the gate
while your grandson, the king,
quivered in fear
behind the walls.
I bled in the mud
for our family.
And as my reward,
I was trundled off
to some dark little cell.
But what do I want?
A little bloody gratitude
would be a start.
Jugglers and singers
require applause.
You are a Lannister.
Do you think I demanded
a garland of roses
every time I suffered
a wound on a battlefield?
Hmm?
Now, I have seven kingdoms
to look after
and three of them
are in open rebellion.
So tell me what you want.
I want what is mine by right.
Jaime is your eldest son,
heir to your lands and titles.
But he is a Kingsguard, forbidden
from marriage or inheritance.
The day Jaime put on
the white cloak,
he gave up his claim
to Casterly Rock.
I am your son and lawful heir.
You want Casterly Rock?
It is mine by right.
We'll find you accommodations
more suited to your name
and as a reward
for your accomplishments
during the battle
of Blackwater Bay.
And when the time is right,
you will be given a position
fit for your talents
so that you can
serve your family
and protect our legacy.
And if you serve faithfully,
you will be rewarded
with a suitable wife.
And I would let myself
be consumed by maggots
before mocking the family name
and making you
heir to Casterly Rock.
- Why?
You ask that?
You, who killed your mother
to come into the world?
You are an ill-made,
spiteful little creature
full of envy, lust,
and low cunning.
Men's laws give you
the right to bear my name
and display my colors since I
cannot prove that you are not mine.
And to teach me humility,
the gods have condemned me
to watch you waddle about
wearing that proud lion
that was my father's sigil
and his father's before him.
But neither gods nor men
will ever compel me
to let you turn Casterly Rock
into your whorehouse.
Go, now.
Speak no more of your rights
to Casterly Rock.
Go.
Oh, one more thing.
The next whore I catch
in your bed I'll hang.
Dorne.
It's going to Dorne.
- Why Dorne?
- It's carrying silk
and it's supposed to bring
back wine in exchange.
But it's not coming back.
The captain's tired
of risking his life
so King's Landing
lords and ladies
can get drunk on better
wine than they deserve.
He's going to stay in Dorne.
Wait out the winter where
it's beautiful and warm.
I met some people in Dorne who
weren't so beautiful and warm.
Don't ruin the game.
I told you,
I don't want to play.
What about that one there?
That one?
It's going to Volantis.
Why?
Because when I got
on a ship in Volantis,
it looked like that one.
That's not how the game works.
You're not supposed to just
blurt out the right answer.
You've got to invent a story
about where the ship
is going and why.
Why should I make up a story
when I know the truth?
Because the truth
is always either
terrible or boring.
Lovely day for it.
Watching the ships.
Lord Baelish.
Might I speak with Lady Sansa
alone for a moment?
I saw your mother not long ago.
She's very eager to see you.
And your sister.
Arya's alive?
You said you'd take me home.
You said King's Landing
was your home.
You are the property
of the crown.
Stealing you would be treason.
If you were to tell
just one person--
- I won't tell anyone.
- How do I know?
Because I'm a terrible liar.
You said so yourself.
Please, Lord Baelish. Tell me what to do.
Tell me when.
I'm waiting for word
on an assignment
that will take me far away
from the capital.
When I set sail,
I might be able
to take you with me.
But you'll need to be ready to
leave on a moment's notice.
You're her handmaiden?
Yes.
And you're his...?
I help manage his affairs.
- He's an important person.
- So is she.
I grew up in the shadow
of her father's castle.
The day she was born,
they rang the bells
from sunrise till sunset.
We've both done
rather well, you and I.
Yes.
Given where we started.
And where is that?
It's not easy for girls like us
to dig our way out.
Watch out for her.
I always do.
Watch out for her with him.
They're growing fast.
Not fast enough.
I can't wait that long.
I need an army.
We'll be in Astapor
by nightfall.
Some say the Unsullied are the
greatest soldiers in the world.
The greatest slave-soldiers
in the world.
The distinction means
a good deal to some people.
Do those people
have any better ideas
about how to put you
on the Iron Throne?
It's too beautiful
a day to argue.
You're right.
Another lovely day
on the high seas.
Don't mock them.
They're the first Dothraki
who have ever been on a ship.
They followed me
across the poison water.
If they'll do it, others will.
And with a true
khalasar--
The Dothraki follow strength
above all, khaleesi.
You'll have a true khalasar
when you prove yourself strong.
And not before.
Your Grace.
I heard you were dead.
Not yet.
I had hoped to speak
to you alone, Your Grace.
We are alone.
Your Grace, you are
the rightful king.
Not only by blood.
You're an honorable man,
a just man.
And there is still
a war to fight.
I am fighting.
By burning prisoners alive?
How would you punish
the infidels, Ser Davos?
I do not judge people
for the gods they worship.
If I did, I'd have
thrown you in the sea
before you ever set foot
on Dragonstone.
- I'm not your enemy.
- You are my enemy.
Was it me you fought
on Blackwater Bay?
Did I set your ships ablaze?
I wasn't there when the wildfire
killed our men by the thousands.
I could have saved those men.
You would have taken the city,
Stannis would now sit
upon his rightful throne,
and you would stand beside him.
But I wasn't there
because you convinced
your king to leave me behind.
Do you hear them screaming?
All those burning men
in the water
crying for their mothers,
for their gods for help?
Until the moment
the Blackwater swallowed them.
Don't despair, Ser Davos.
What I told your son is true.
Death by fire
is the purest death.
This woman is evil!
She's the mother of demons.
Take him to the dungeon
and lock him in a cell.
- Your Grace!
- Come on.
You've chosen
the darkness, Ser Davos.
- She will destroy us all!
- I will pray for you.
Your Grace!
Halt. Down.
Why have we stopped?
It's Lady Margaery, Your Grace.
What is she doing?
Who gave her permission?
My lady. We should
have guards, my lady.
Why?
Pardon me.
Stop, my lady.
You'll ruin your dress.
I have others.
Would you like to speak
with her, Your Grace?
No.
He was a soldier.
He went to fight on the walls
when the ships came
into Blackwater Bay.
He never came back.
And your mother?
She died when she had me.
Bad men wanted
to come into this city
and do terrible things,
but your father stopped them.
Whenever you look
at this knight,
I want you to remember
your father.
He wasn't a knight.
He was just a soldier.
And what do knights
swear to do?
Protect the weak
and uphold the good.
Your father did that.
Be proud of him.
Was your father a soldier, too?
You should be proud, too.
Under King Joffrey's
leadership,
your fathers saved the city.
They saved us all.
From now on, we're going
to take care of you.
All of you.
Come to me for whatever
you need to feed them,
clothe them, or house them.
Directly to me.
- Your Grace.
Please, sit.
Sit.
I do apologize, my lady.
Small council meetings.
At what point
does it become treason
to waste the king's time?
That's a lovely gown, my lady.
Yes, it suits you perfectly.
I imagine you might
be rather cold.
The climate is a bit more forgiving
back in Highgarden, Your Grace.
Shall I have them bring
you a shawl, my lady?
I am touched by your
concern, Your Grace.
Luckily for us Tyrells,
our blood runs quite warm.
- Doesn't it, Loras?
- Yes.
Loras, isn't the queen's
gown magnificent?
The fabric, the embroidery,
the metalwork.
I've never seen
anything like it.
You might find a bit
of armor quite useful
once you become queen.
Perhaps before.
Joffrey tells me you stopped
your carriage at Flea Bottom
on your way back from
the sept this morning.
Yes. I paid a visit
to an orphanage
the High Septon told me about.
Margaery does a great deal of work
with the poor back in Highgarden.
The lowest among us are no different from
the highest if you give them a chance
and approach them
with an open heart.
An open heart is what
you'll get in Flea Bottom
if you're not careful, my dear.
Not long ago, we were
attacked by a mob there.
We had a full complement
of guards that didn't stop them.
The king barely escaped
with his life.
My mother's always had
a penchant for drama.
Facts become less and less
important to her
as she grows older.
Our lives were never
truly in danger.
You're right, of course.
But you are your father's son.
We can't all have
a king's bravery.
Hunger turns men into beasts.
I'm glad House Tyrell has been
able to help in this regard.
They tell me 100 wagons arrive
daily now from the Reach.
Wheat, barley, apples.
We've had a blessed harvest.
And, of course, it's our
duty to assist the capital
in time of need.
Well, as Ser Loras said,
Lady Margaery has done
this sort of...
charitable work before.
I'm sure she knows
what she's doing.
I'm sure she does.
The Unsullied have stood here
for a day and a night
with no food or water.
They will stand
until they drop.
Such is their obedience.
They may suit my needs.
Tell me of their training.
They begin their
training at 5.
Every day they drill
from dawn to dusk
until they have mastered
the shortsword,
the shield,
and the 3 spears.
Only one boy in 4 survives
this rigorous training.
Their discipline
and loyalty are absolute.
They fear nothing.
Even the bravest men
fear death.
My master says
the Unsullied are not men.
Death means nothing to them.
He begs you attend to this
carefully, Your Grace.
Tell the good master
there is no need.
My master points out
that men don't need nipples.
To win his shield,
an Unsullied must go to the
slave marts with a silver mark,
find a newborn and kill it
before its mother's eyes.
This way, my master says,
we make certain
there is no weakness
left in them.
You take a babe
from its mother's arms,
kill it as she watches, and pay
for her pain with a silver coin?
My master would like you to
know that the silver is paid
to the baby's owner,
not the mother.
How many do you have to sell?
8,000.
Master Kraznys asks
that you please hurry.
Many other buyers
are interested.
8,000 dead babies.
The Unsullied
are a means to an end.
Once I own them,
these men--
They're not men.
Not anymore.
Once I own an army of
slaves, what will I be?
Do you think these slaves
will have better lives
serving Kraznys and men
like him or serving you?
You'll be fair to them.
You won't mutilate them
to make a point.
You won't order them
to murder babies.
You'll see they're properly
fed and sheltered.
A great injustice
has been done to them.
Closing your eyes
will not undo it.
The warlocks.
I owe you my life, ser.
The honor is mine,
my queen.
You know this man?
I know him
as one of the greatest fighters
the Seven Kingdoms has ever seen
and as the Lord Commander
of Robert Baratheon's
Kingsguard.
King Robert is dead.
I have been searching
for you, Daenerys Stormborn,
to ask your forgiveness.
I was sworn to protect
your family.
I failed them.
I am Barristan Selmy,
Kingsguard to your father.
Allow me to join
your Queensguard
and I will not fail you again.