and three-eyed ravens
and black magic?
I don't want you talking to him
till we get to Castle Black.
We're not going to Castle Black.
Jon Snow isn't there.
Bran needs to find
the raven beyond the Wall.
Oh, no, I'm not
going back there.
I promised your maester I'd get you
to Castle Black and no further.
You won't win.
You don't have the discipline.
- You don't know how to fight together.
- You don't know that.
If you attack the Wall
you'll die, all of you.
All of us.
I can't force them
to meet us in the field.
- Casterly Rock can't run away.
- Can you do it?
There is only one person
in this kingdom
with that kind of army.
Walder Frey.
We will do whatever we can to
give Lord Frey what he needs.
Our father requires Lord Edmure
to wed one of his daughters.
- You were sent here to kill me?
- I don't want to.
What do your captains
have to say about that?
You should ask them.
Will you fight for me?
The Second Sons are yours
and so is Daario Naharis.
My sword is yours,
my life is yours,
my heart is yours.
- Is that the Blackwater?
- Where do you think I'm taking you?
- Back to King's Landing.
- That's the Red Fork.
I'm taking you to the Twins.
Your uncle's marrying
one of the Frey girls.
Your mother and brother
will be there
and they'll pay me for you.
That rain will cost
us another day.
Lord Frey will take
this delay as a slight.
- He's getting the wedding he wanted.
- He's getting a wedding.
It was a king he wanted.
It's come for the baby.
You stay back!
No, you can't have him.
No!
Are you sure about this?
No.
It's dangerous.
If we take Tywin's
castle from him,
the lords of Westeros will
realize he's not invincible.
Take his home,
take his gold, take his power.
Why are you telling me?
You begged me not to send Theon
to negotiate with his father
and I ignored your advice.
Now Winterfell is burnt
to the ground,
the North is overrun
with ironborn,
and Bran and Rickon are gone.
So Casterly Rock...
I'm asking your advice.
We have enough men?
If Walder Frey cooperates.
If reinforcements arrive
from King's Landing
before we take the castle...
we'll be caught between
Tywin's army and the sea.
We'll lose the war and die
the way Father died.
Or worse.
Show them how it feels
to lose what they love.
My honored guests...
be welcome within my walls
and at my table.
I extend to you my hospitality
and protection
in the light of the Seven.
We thank you for your
hospitality, my lord.
I have come to make
my apologies, my lord,
and to beg your forgiveness.
Don't beg my forgiveness,
Your Grace.
It wasn't me you spurned.
It was my girls.
One of them was supposed
to be queen.
Now none of them are.
This is Arwyen my daughter.
My daughter Walda,
my daughter Derwa,
my daughter Waldra.
My eldest granddaughters
Ginia and Neila.
Serra and Sarra,
granddaughters, twins.
You could have had either.
Could have had both
for all I care.
My granddaughter Marianne.
My granddaughter Freya.
My granddaughter...
Wertha.
Waldra.
Waldina.
- I'm Merry.
- Fine.
And here's my youngest
daughter Shirei,
though she hasn't bled yet.
Clearly you don't have
the patience for all that.
My ladies.
All men should keep their
word, kings most of all.
I was pledged to marry one
of you and I broke that vow.
The fault is not with you.
Any man would be lucky
to have any one of you.
I did what I did
not to slight you,
but because I loved another.
I know these words
cannot set right
the wrong I have done
to you and your house.
I beg your forgiveness
and pledge to do
all I can to make amends
so the Freys of the Crossing
and the Starks of Winterfell
may once again be friends.
Very good.
There she is.
Come closer.
Let me have a look at you.
Still can't see you.
Old eyes.
Love.
That's what the Starks
of Winterfell call it, eh?
Very honorable.
I call it a pretty face.
Mmm, very pretty.
Prettier than this lot,
that's for sure.
Very shapely as well.
Oh, you try to hide her
under that dress.
If you wanted to hide her,
you shouldn't have brought her
here in the first place.
I can always see
what's going on
beneath a dress.
Been at this a long time.
I bet when you take
that dress off,
everything stays
right where it is.
Doesn't drop an inch.
Your king says he betrayed
me for love.
I say he betrayed me
for firm tits
and a tight fit.
And I can respect that.
When I was your age,
I'd have broken 50 oaths
to get into that
without a second thought.
Well, I've enough room
in the hall for you lot.
We'll set up tents outside
with food and ale
for the rest of your men.
Thank you, my lord.
Well, let's get ready.
The wine will flow red
and the music will play loud
and we'll put
this mess behind us.
Where?
There.
It's a back gate.
My men use it when they
visit Yunkai's bed slaves.
Your men, but not you?
I have no
interest in slaves.
A man cannot make love
to property.
This is where
we enter the city.
Very few guards.
They know me.
They let me inside--
We're not gonna sneak
an army through a back gate.
I kill the guards.
I take your two best men
and lead them through the back
streets, which I know well,
and open the front gates.
Then comes the army.
Once the walls are breached,
the city will fall in hours.
Or perhaps you'll lead Grey
Worm and me to the slaughter,
cutting the head off our army.
The masters of Yunkai
will pay you your fee
and you won't have
to split it three ways
'cause you've already
slaughtered your partners.
You have
a very suspicious mind.
In my experience, only dishonest
people think this way.
You command the Unsullied.
What do you think?
You leave tonight.
Very good.
We'll prepare.
Ser Jorah.
You can use an extra sword.
You're the Queensguard,
Ser Barristan.
Your place is by the queen.
If we are truly
her loyal servants,
we'll do whatever
needs to be done
no matter the cost,
no matter our pride.
We're west of Castle Black,
but the Nightfort's
closest to us.
It was the first
castle on the Wall.
The Watch abandoned it during
the reign of King Jaehaerys I.
Too big.
Impossible to maintain.
Other than Castle Black itself,
the Nightfort's
the perfect castle for us.
It's got a secret sally port,
the Black Gate,
as old as the Wall itself.
No one's used it
in centuries most likely.
It leads through the Wall
right down into the Nightfort,
if one knows how to find it,
which, it just
so happens, I do.
How do you know all that?
I read about it
in a very old book.
You know all that
from staring at marks on paper?
Yes.
You're like a wizard.
Our father used to tell us
that no wildling ever looked
upon the Wall and lived.
Here we are.
Alive.
Remember what happens
to children who run.
I'm your father
and I'll do the talking.
The roads have gone
right to hell, haven't they?
Cracked 3 spokes
this morning.
- Need a hand?
- Need about 8 hands.
Oh!
Got to get this
salt pork to the Twins
in time for the wedding.
Many thanks.
Don't!
Don't kill him.
Dead rats don't squeak.
You're so dangerous,
aren't you?
Saying scary things
to little girls.
Killing little boys
and old people.
A real hard man you are.
More than anyone you know.
You're wrong.
I know a killer.
- A real killer.
- That so?
You'd be like a kitten to him.
He'd kill you
with his little finger.
That him?
- No.
- Good.
Don't kill him.
Please.
Please don't.
You're very kind.
Someday it'll get you killed.
Where are we?
The Gift, I think.
Brandon the Builder
gave all this land
south of the Wall
to the Night's Watch
for their sustenance
and support.
Maester Luwin taught me that.
Doesn't seem to be supporting
anyone at the moment.
It's good land
and there's no war up here.
Why leave?
Wildlings.
Sorry.
But they come over
the Wall and raid,
steal, carry off women.
Old Nan said they turn
your skull into a cup
and make you drink
your own blood from it.
That's what Old Nan said.
There's a storm coming.
I don't see any--
It's as good a place
to shelter as any.
We can drink some blood
while we wait.
I don't need much.
Only one old man
and 8 good horses.
What's one old man
doing with 8 horses?
He breeds them for the Watch.
How's he keep folks
from stealing them?
The Watch protects him.
Not today they don't.
He's selling horses,
he's got some gold in there.
- And proper steel.
- Let's carve him up.
We just take the horses and go.
The old man's no threat.
I keep telling you.
He's an old man.
A spear through the heart's
a better way to die
than coughing up your last with
no one but your horses to hear.
The Watch might send a few men
looking for a horse thief.
They'll send a lot more
to hunt down murderers.
I hope so.
Killing crows
in their castle is tough.
Killing them out here
in the open,
that's what we do.
Spread out.
Surround the hut and move in.
Ygritte!
Clear the barn!
No one's going to believe you're a
hog farmer if you eat them all.
Best part of the animal.
Don't worry.
They're still there.
I know they're still there.
You check every 5 minutes
like you're afraid
they're gonna move.
I'm not afraid.
Of course you are.
You're almost there
and you're afraid
you won't make it.
The closer you get,
the worse the fear gets.
No point in trying to hide
behind that face.
I know fear when I see it.
Seen it a lot.
I knew fear
when I saw it in you.
You're afraid of fire.
When Beric's sword
went up in flames,
you looked like
a scared little girl.
And I know why, too.
I heard what
your brother did to you.
Pressed your face to the fire
like you're a nice
juicy mutton chop.
That give you some ideas?
Might do.
Go ahead, then.
You might get away.
Might even make it
there on your own.
They're just over the river.
The closest you've
been to family
since Ilyn Payne
snipped your daddy's neck.
Someday I'm gonna put
a sword through your eye
and out the back of your skull.
How are we going
to get past the Wall?
My uncle said
it's 700 feet high.
How did you get past it?
Got in a boat and rowed
past the Bay of Seals.
It would take us two months
to get to the Bay of Seals.
Some climb straight up the ice.
Even Hodor's not strong enough to
climb the Wall with me on his back.
Hodor.
19 castles guard the Wall.
- Only 3 are still manned.
- Hodor!
One of those abandoned fortresses
will give us a way through.
My uncle said the gates were
sealed with ice and stone
when the castles were deserted.
Well, we'll have
to open them up again.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- There's a rider out there.
Just one?
- There's more.
- Hodor!
Shh. Shh.
- It's just thunder, sweet giant.
- Hodor.
I yield.
- I yield.
- Wildlings.
Where's Shaggydog and Summer?
Hunting.
Hodor!
- Shh, quiet, Hodor.
- Hodor!
Make him shut up.
If they hear us...
- Hush, Hodor. No-- no more Hodoring.
- Hodor!
- Hodor, calm down.
- You need to keep quiet.
- They're gonna hear us.
Hodor, be quiet.
- Ah! Hodor!
- Hodor, calm down.
- Hodor! Hodor!
- Hodor, be quiet!
What did you do?
Nothing.
I don't know.
What's that?
That's a horse dying.
Bring them over here.
That was the last of them.
The rest are dead.
I heard shouting up there.
Thunder.
I know the difference
between shouting and thunder.
Maybe it's ghosts.
That won't help you, grandpa.
Where you riding?
Doesn't matter now, does it?
No, it doesn't matter now.
Cut his throat or he'll
tell the crows we're here.
You understand.
Let me stand at least.
Let me go
with a bit of dignity.
Make the crow kill him.
You're one of us now.
Prove it.
The wolves are out there.
I can't do it by choice.
I don't know how.
It happens in my dreams.
You're a warg, Bran.
It's in your blood.
I can't.
You just did with him.
A wolf is nothing
compared to that.
She looks sharp.
Do it.
I told you.
He's still one of them.
Go on, boy.
Go on!
He's a crow.
He'll always be a crow.
And here's his crow wife
guarding him.
He'll stab us in the back
first chance he gets.
Kill him.
- He's one of them.
- No!
Do you hear me?
You're not gonna die
for one of them.
Do it.
They'll find us if you don't.
You were right the whole time.
Hyah!
When you hear a
songbird's whistle, you come.
I'm a great whistler.
The greatest in the land.
Daario Naharis.
That one was quick.
- There may be others.
- I doubt it.
The Yunkish prefer to let their
slaves do their fighting for them.
That's what you call
a few guards?
Come on!
What do you got, huh?
Lord Edmure...
I hope I'm not
a disappointment to you.
You're a delight
to me, my lady.
You may now cloak the bride
and bring her under
your protection.
In the sight of the Seven,
I hereby seal these two souls,
binding them as one
for eternity.
Look upon each other
and say the words.
Father, Smith,
Warrior, Mother,
Maiden, Crone, Stranger...
- I am hers...
- I am his...
- and she is mine...
- and he is mine...
...from this day
until the end of my days.
- Is that safe?
- They're long gone.
You were right.
I can get inside Summer's
mind whenever I want.
Of course you can.
North of the Wall
there are wildlings
who can control
all sorts of animals.
But you did a lot
more than that.
You got inside Hodor's mind.
They can't do that
north of the Wall?
No one can do that...
anywhere.
When I was looking
through Summer's eyes,
- I saw Jon.
- Where?
He was with the wildlings.
They tried to kill him,
but he got away.
He'll be heading back
to Castle Black, then.
That's where we should go.
For all we know, Castle
Black's already under attack.
- If this many wildlings got through--
- I already told you.
I'm not going
north of the Wall.
Everything Jojen
told me is true.
You saw what I did to Hodor.
I have to find
the three-eyed raven.
Listen to me, little lord.
Don't worry.
I'm not asking you
to come with me.
It won't be safe for Rickon.
Me?
I'm coming with you.
No.
You and Osha and Shaggydog
head for the Last Hearth.
The Umbers are our bannermen.
They'll protect you.
I'm coming with you.
I'm your brother.
I have to protect you.
Right now I have
to protect you.
Robb's at war and I'm
going beyond the Wall.
If something happens to us,
you're the heir to Winterfell.
Would you know how
to find the Last Hearth?
You southerners build your big
castles and you never move.
You're easy to find.
We're not southerners.
And I don't want to leave you.
Shh, shh.
Come here, little soldier.
You and me, we're gonna
have some adventures.
You don't have to do
any of this.
Your family took me in
and was good to me when
they had no cause to be.
Shh.
We'll be fine, you and me.
The Umbers are great warriors.
Even I heard
about them growing up.
They'll teach you
how to swing a sword.
I know how to swing a sword.
You're leaving now? It's
the middle of the night.
I learned to walk in darkness.
Say your good-byes,
little man.
Keep this one safe.
He means the world to me.
We've been waiting a long time.
Haven't we?
I don't know, you tell me.
How long does it take
to sack a city?
It was just as you said.
They did not believe
until it was too late.
Their slave soldiers
threw down their spears
and surrendered.
And Daario Naharis?
The city is yours, my queen.
They're good, aren't they?
They ought to be
because they cost enough.
Look at the crowd there.
He complained
about this marriage
the entire ride from Riverrun,
and now look at him.
The gods
love to reward a fool.
- Uncle.
- What?
He's my nephew.
I love him.
And he's a damned fool.
Don't you drink, Lord Bolton?
Never do, my lady.
Dulls the senses.
That's the point.
Didn't you marry
one of these Frey girls?
Aye.
Lord Walder let me choose
any of his granddaughters
and promised me the girl's
weight in silver as a dowry.
So I have a fat young bride.
I hope she makes you
very happy.
Well, she's made me very rich.
Pardon, my lord, my lady.
I need to find
a tree to piss on.
My mother's alone
with Roose Bolton.
I should rescue her.
Your mother is less
in need of rescue
than any woman I've ever met.
Be kind.
She's finally starting
to like you.
And I like her.
But if she had her way,
I would be back in Volantis
playing my harp and you
would be sitting over there
eating blackberries
out of Roslin Frey's hand.
Perhaps I've made
a terrible mistake.
Striking your king
is an act of treason.
No, don't.
Don't insult them.
Your Grace.
The septon has prayed
his prayers,
some words were said,
and Lord Edmure
has wrapped my daughter
in a cloak.
But they are not yet
man and wife.
A sword needs a sheath.
And a wedding needs a bedding.
What does my sire say?
To bed! To bed! To bed!
If you think the time
is right, Lord Walder,
by all means, let us bed them.
To bed! To bed! To bed!
Go on!
Oh!
Careful now, ladies.
Once you set that monster free,
there's no caging him again.
To bed! To bed! To bed!
Poor girl.
Every bride suffers the same.
I'm sure you endured
yours with grace.
Oh, Ned forbade it.
He said it wouldn't be right if he broke
a man's jaw on our wedding night.
That is a very strange custom.
I suppose it does seem strange
from a foreigner's perspective.
It seems normal to you?
It's a tradition.
Without the bedding ceremony,
there's no real proof
the lord and lady
consummated their marriage.
But there are other ways
of providing proof.
Boy or girl?
I don't know.
But if it's a boy, I know
what we should name him.
Oh, do you?
It seems to me the father should
have some say in his son's naming.
Eddard.
Don't you want to teach
little Ned Stark
how to ride horses?
I do.
Go on, line 'em up!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Where are you going?
Got salt pork for the feast.
The feast is over.
Doesn't sound
like it's over.
If I tell you
it's over, it's over.
Turn this cart around
and get the hell out of here.
Got pig's feet, too.
Are you soft in the head?
Turn this cart around.
Your Grace.
I feel I've been remiss
in my duties.
I've given you meat
and wine and music,
but I haven't shown you
the hospitality you deserve.
My king has married
and I owe my new queen
a wedding gift.
Robb!
You ready to
head home to Winterfell, right?
Feast over yet, is it?
Aye, it's over.
Follow him.
It's too late.
The King in the North arises.
Lord Walder!
Lord Walder, enough!
Let it end!
Please.
He is my son.
My first son.
Let him go and I swear
that we will forget this.
I swear it by
the old gods and new.
We will take no vengeance.
You already swore me one oath
right here in my castle.
You swore by all the gods your
son would marry my daughter!
Take me for a
hostage, but let Robb go.
Robb, get up.
Get up and walk out.
Please!
And why would I
let him do that?
On my honor as a Tully,
on my honor as a Stark,
let him go
or I will cut
your wife's throat.
I'll find another.
Mother.
The Lannisters send
their regards.